<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- 
news.xml
9/15/2013
Jay Lawson
This file defines defines a set of news item that will display in the daily report frame of MekHQ. 

Here is a description of what goes in each newsItem tag
headline - This is the headline that will appear in the daily report and in the title of the full article.
           This item should always be defined.
date - the date of the news item in YYYY-MM-DD format. This is required.
desc - a longer description of the news item. This is optional, but must be present for the "read more" link. 
       It should always be surrounded by <![CDATA[stuff]]> and may contain html markup.
service - an optional tag for the news service doing the reporing
location - an optional tag for the location of the news report
 -->
<news>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Mercenary Treachery</headline>
		<date>3068-01-02</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[It seems that for every mercenary command of sterling character (such as Wolf’s Dragoons, the Kell Hounds or the Twelfth Vegan Rangers), 
		there is one for whom money is the only thing that matters. The Word of Blake highlighted this with deadly clarity when they bought Waco’s Rangers, Smithson’s 
		Chinese Bandits, the Tiger Sharks and the 51st Dark Panzer Jaegers and unleashed them on Harlech. Now to this roll of dishonor must be added the Broadsword Legion. 
		Hired by Wolf’s Dragoons in their moment of need, the Legion turned on their employers as the Dragoons battled to defend their homes from the onslaught of the Blakists’ 
		Sixth and Tenth Divisions.<p>At the height of this second battle of Outreach, just as it appeared the defenders were gaining the upper hand, the Broadsword Legion launched a 
		furious assault on the rear of the Dragoons’ Wolf Spiders Battalion. Pinned between the Legion and the Blakist Diplomacy of Force III-Alpha, the Wolf Spiders (proud holders 
		of the Black Widow Battalion legacy) were almost annihilated before they could rally. That costly act of treachery further weakened the Dragoons. In an apparent effort to 
		finish off the famed mercenaries once and for all, the Blakists reportedly launched devastating strategic attacks against the planet from orbit.<p>Across the Inner Sphere, 
		the same question is being asked: Who will next turn their coat? Which mercenary command will turn on its employers and do the evil bidding of the Word of Blake? This 
		fear has already led to tragedy on Epsilon Indi, where the Com Guards Second Division launched an unprovoked attack on the Tooth of Ymir. Reportedly, relations between the 
		Com Guards and the mercenaries had been strained ever since the mercenary unit arrived on-world.<p>Faced with overwhelming odds, Colonel Shadwell wisely ordered the battered 
		Tooth to surrender. Following an exhaustive investigation, Precentor Regis Grandi has reluctantly been forced to concede that no tangible proof exists linking the Tooth with 
		the Word of Blake. The Tooth of Ymir, now under the minimum strength stipulated by their contract, is reportedly headed for Arc-Royal to rebuild. In the meantime, many mercenary 
		commanders are left nervously wondering how long it will be before their equally nervous employers turn on them.]]></desc>
		<service>INN</service>
		<location>Outreach</location>
	</newsItem>
</news>