<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
news.xml
9/15/2013
Jay Lawson
Updated
9/9/2017
Adam Brant
Updated 6/6/2020
Jason Schmetzer

This file defines defines a set of news item that will display in the daily report frame of MekHQ. Sources are provided where available.

Here is a description of what goes in each newsItem tag.
headline - This is the headline that will appear in the daily report and in the title of the full article. This item should always be defined.
date - the date of the news item in yyyy-MM-dd format. This is required. If the "dd" part is missing, the day will be rolled randomly (each campaign will have its own random seed for that). Same if only the year is supplied. Finally, the year can be of the form "302X", which will generate a random day within that decade.
desc - a longer description of the news item. This is optional, but must be present for the "read more" link. It should always be surrounded by <![CDATA[stuff]]> and may contain html markup.
service - an optional tag for the news service doing the reporting
location - an optional tag for the location of the news report
 -->

 <!--
Notes on Canonicity
Feb 2020 - A section for non-canon events has been added after all of the Era data.
Published sources deemed non-canon are: BattleTechnology Magazine, Star-Date Magazine, 'Mech Magazine, Video Games, Battletech Cartoon series, Battletech Comic books, Battletech Card Game.
Information veracity as described in the 25 Years of Art & Fiction of "Story Fiction" and Sourcebook Fiction" are included based on the descriptions on Sarna.net. Canon rumours are also included if a source can be determined, even if proven false at a later date via a different or more complete source.
-->

<news>
 <!-- Star League Era (2005 - 2780) -->
	<!-- Age of War - First Exodus (2005 - 2242) -->
	<!-- Age of War - Second Exodus (2243 - 2398) -->
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Admiral James McKenna Made Fleet Admiral of the Alliance Navy</headline><!-- Source: The Star League -->
		<date>2295</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[Admiral James McKenna has been promoted to Fleet Admiral following the retirement of his predecessor, leaving him in control of the Alliance Navy. We at TNS wish Fleet Admiral McKenna the best of luck with his new position.]]></desc>
		<service>TNS</service>
		<location>Terra</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Launch of the WarShip Dreadnought</headline><!-- Source: MUL Online -->
		<date>2300</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[There was only one opinion among those who were present at the launching of the <em>Dreadnought</em> today, and that was expressed in the three words "a great success." The ceremony was indeed a success from every point of view, and will long live in the memory of all who were priviledged to be spectators of it, sadly few they may have been. At the ceremony's conclusion Fleet Admiral McKenna declared the creation of an Alliance Navy that all can be proud of, with the TAS <em>Dreadnought</em> as the resurgent fleet's flagship.]]></desc>
		<service>TNS</service>
		<location>Terra</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Director-General McKenna has Fallen</headline><!-- Source: The Star League -->
		<date>2338</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[Director-General McKenna passed away from cancer yesterday, surrounded by the family he loved so dearly. We at TNS join the entire Hegemony in mourning the loss of a great man, and wishing his family well through the difficult days ahead.]]></desc>
		<service>TNS</service>
		<location>Terra</location>
	</newsItem>
	<!-- Age of War (2399 - 2570) -->
	<newsItem>
		<headline>A new shuttle introduced, A Life Boat</headline><!-- Source: Technical Readout: 3057 Revised -->
		<date>2478</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Introducing a new lifesaving vessel for DropShips and JumpShips who suffer accidents in space, we have the Life Boat. This vessel is not designed for reentry or thrust to escape the area. However, with a larger radar signature and solar sail the odds of rescue are increased over previous lifesaving vessels.</p>]]></desc>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Regulan Hussars upgraded to brigade size</headline><!-- Source: House Marik (The Free Worlds League) -->
		<date>2478</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The Regulan Hussars, long a regiment-sized unit of the Principality of Regulus, has been reinforced to brigade size. This is to help it better handle possible invasions from its enemies, the Terran Hegemony.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>IMI</service>
		<location>Regulus</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Stinger vs Wasp</headline><!-- Source: Technical Readout: 3025 -->
		<date>2479</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Earthwerks Inc, annouced today the <em>Stinger</em>, a light 'Mech to rival the <em>Wasp</em> as the premier recon 'Mech of the Terran Hegemony.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>TNS</service>
		<location>Terra</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Elizabeth Cameron takes Director-General Position</headline><!-- Source: The Star League -->
		<date>2479</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Following a serious health issue, Theodore Cameron has decided to step down from the rigors of the Director-General. His daughter Elizabeth Cameron will be taking over the throne of the Terran Hegemony. We wish the former Director-General a speedy recovery and look forward to the new reign of Elizabeth Cameron.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>TNS</service>
		<location>Terra</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Commando to be Upgraded</headline><!-- Source: Technical Readout: 3039 -->
		<date>2480</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Following recent advances in both 'Mech design and electronics, Coventry Defense Conglomerate has release news of a new COM-1D variant of their <em>Commando</em> light 'Mech. Sacrificing two tons of armor allows the <em>Commando</em> to carry an SRM-6.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>DBC</service>
		<location>Coventry</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Kintetsu Stellar Systems Announces New DropShip</headline><!-- Source: Handbook: House Kurita -->
		<date>2480</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Kintetsu Stellar Systems has started production of a new DropShip, the <em>Hoshiryokou</em>. This class of DropShip, while small, can handle 85 tons internally while carrying 10 Cargo containers of 10 tons each.</p>]]></desc>
		<location>Luthien</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Toro of Taurian Concordat</headline><!-- Source: Era Digest: Age of War -->
		<date>2481</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Taurus WarWorks annouced today, the <em>Toro TR-A-1</em>. A 35 ton light 'Mech armed with a PPC and two LRM-5s, we see this as a long-range threat in the years to come.</p>]]></desc>
		<service></service>
		<location>Taurus</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Close Range Crossbow</headline><!-- Source: MUL Online -->
		<date>2481</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>In a interesting annoucement today, Arcturan Arms annouced the introduction of a new variant on their long-range <em>Crossbow</em> 'Mech. The CRS-6C will now be packing an Autocannon/10. However, this comes at the lost of its LRMs and one medium laser. Only time will tell if this new variant will survive the rigors of the battlefield.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>DBC</service>
		<location>Arcturus</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Brion Marik Re-elected</headline><!-- Source: Handbook: House Marik -->
		<date>2481</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>For the second time, Brion Marik has been elected into the Captain-General post.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>IMI</service>
		<location>Atreus</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>New Chancellor of the Capellan Confederation</headline><!-- Source: House Liao (The Capellan Confederation) -->
		<date>2482</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Raxal Liao has come of age and the Regency has ended. The new Chancellor thanked the Duke of Sian for his service and then promptly stated that he did not wish to rule. The 13th Chancellor stepped down 12 minutes later. He was quoted as saying "I perferred to be a scholar and scientist rather than Chancellor." The 14th Chancellor, Hendrick Liao, has taken over the reins of state with aplomp.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CBS</service>
		<location>Capella</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Capellan Confederation's Firebee Makeover</headline><!-- Source: Technical Readout: 3075 -->
		<date>2483</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>A second-generation version of the Capellan Confederation's 'Mech has been released. This new 'Mech designated FRB-2E, removes its LRM for two more SRMs and a large laser. Giving it that added long range punch without the limits of ammo.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CBS</service>
		<location>Boardwalk</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>New power in Marik</headline><!-- Source: House Marik (The Free Worlds League) -->
		<date>2484</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Pounding its way onto the battlefield in Marik Guard colors is the newest BattleMech force outside of the Terran Hegemony's control.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>IMI</service>
		<location>Marik</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>First Regulan Hussars attack Lopez</headline><!-- Source: Rolling Thunder -->
		<date>2485</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The First Regulan Hussars attacked a Capellan Confederation Heavy Tank Regiment marking their first time in combat. However, technical issues along with lack of training resulted in their first lost as well.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>IMI</service>
		<location>Marik</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Fusiliers of Oriente form new unit</headline><!-- Source: Field Manual: Free Worlds League -->
		<date>2485</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The Fusilers of Oriente formed the Ducal Guard today.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>IMI</service>
		<location>Oriente</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Draconis Combine unveils new DropShip</headline><!-- Source: Handbook: House Kurita -->
		<date>2485</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The Draconis Combine annouced the <em>Gaajian</em> System Patrol Boat to gathered members of the press today. This new DropShip class will be providing intra-system escort to merchants as well as providing customs and interdiction duties.</p>]]></desc>
		<service></service>
		<location>Luthien</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>The Apostle Removed from Service</headline><!-- Source: Experimental Technical Readout: Primitives, Volume 5 -->
		<date>2485</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p><em>Apostle Self-Propelled Artillery</em> has reached the end of its long and glorious career in the Terran Hegemony today when officals removed it from the TO&E of the military.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>TNS</service>
		<location>Terra</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Commando Upgrade Again?</headline><!-- Source: Technical Readout: 3039 -->
		<date>2486</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Coventry Defense Conglomerate seeing the tactics of pilots of their light 'Mech has come out with a new variant which increases armor in addition to adding an SRM-4 and replacing its large laser with a medium one.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>DBC</service>
		<location>Coventry</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Thorn takes the field, sure to be a pain</headline><!-- Source: Technical Readout: 2750 -->
		<date>2490</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>A new design focused on fire support for recon lances has been fielded over the last few months after successful trials. the <em>Thorn</em> is one of the lightest 'Mechs available at 20 tons but packs not only a pair of medium lasers, but a 5-pack long range missile system to provide a long-range punch for its lance-mates.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>TNS</service>
		<location>Terra</location>
	</newsItem>
	<!-- Star League (2571 - 2780) -->
<!-- HPG Network Activated -->  
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Mister Watson. Come here. I want to see you.</headline><!-- Source: Sourcebook: ComStar -->
		<date>2630-01-01</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[These were the first words successfully sent through the new hyperpulse generator by First Lord Nicholas Cameron himself. The message, sent through this new faster than light communication system, was received immediately. We predict that the implementation of this revolutionary technology will vastly improve interstellar communications, as it can send messages instantaneously at distances of up to 50 light-years.]]></desc>
		<service>TNS</service>
		<location>Terra</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Broadcast Message</headline><!-- Source: Sourcebook: ComStar -->
		<date>2630-01-01</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>This is a broadcast test message of the HPG link system.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>SLCOMNET</service>
		<location>Terra</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>SLDF fields new technology</headline><!-- Source: MUL online -->
		<date>2630</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>A new era of warfighting is upon us as one of the most technologically advanced BattleMechs has completed field testing on Terra. The <em>Exterminator</em> has several new advances integrated that are still listed as classified. While several reports indicate that it will bring about a change in doctrine for several decades, the secrecy lends one to believe that the SLDF has a special mission in mind for this new 'Mech.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>TNN</service>
		<location>Terra</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>First Lord names new Director-General</headline><!-- Source: The Star League -->
		<date>2630</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>A new leader for the Terran Hegemony has been named by the First Lord. Joseph Cameron, son of First Lord Nicholas Cameron, has been named as the Director-General. Having been the subject of some recent scandal, this appointment is a shock to many nobles and rumors are already swirling about additional, potentially emberassing, details yet to be released.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>TNN</service>
		<location>Terra</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>New aerospace fighter takes flight</headline><!-- Source: MUL online -->
		<date>2630</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The latest design from Imstar Aerospace recently cleared testing for manufacture. Corporate officials are stating that the <em>Cheetah</em> is aptly named, the fastest aerospace fighter currently available. An anonymous source within Imstar has mentioned that this speed does not come without compromise and that the engine consumes fuel mush more quickly than many other fighters of its size.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>TNN</service>
		<location>Terra</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Amendment passed on Executive Order 34</headline><!-- Source: The Star League -->
		<date>2630</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Executive Order 35 has been released to the Houses of the Inner Sphere which ammends EO 34 from 2606. This ammendment allows for any criminal who attempts to join the SLDF to be denied pending final judicial determination from the appropriate government. This changes the order that no government could interfere with recruiting of SLDF personnel. Several officials stated that it was overdue and that any personnel that used the loophole should be turned back over to the government for trial.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>TNN</service>
		<location>Terra</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>New JumpShip launched</headline><!-- Source: Technical Readout: 3057 -->
		<date>2631</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>After several years of design and testing, the <em>Invader</em>-class JumpShip has been launched. Several radical changes from typical design have made this one of the most technologically advanced ships ever seen. Boasting room for over 1,000 tons of cargo and the ability to carry three DropShips, this ship has both commercial and military applications. One notable inclusion is onboard hydroponics facilities for long-term operations away from resupply as well as trade missions to less agriculturally abundant locations.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>TNN</service>
		<location>Terra</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem><!-- ISSUE - ERROR -->
		<headline>Iona Light Shipyards new fighter dead in space?</headline><!-- Source: MUL online -->
		<date>2631</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>After several years of design and testing, the <em>Rogue</em>-class JumpShip has been launched. Increasing cost and changes in design, the new aerospace fighter unveiled this year is seeing harsh criticism. Poor maneuverability and reliance on resupply are just two of the many factors that are seen as just more examples of over engineering.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>TNN</service>
		<location>Terra</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Replacement for aging bugs revealed to military commanders</headline><!-- Source: Technical Readout: 2750 -->
		<date>2742</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>An announcement by Mitchell Vehicles has generated mixed feelings about their newest BattleMech chassis. The <em>Mercury</em> was designed to replace older models of the <em>Wasp</em> and <em>Stinger</em> and has left some force commanders wondering if it can stand up to its promises. While the specifics of the new chassis are still being revealed, a press meeting with Mitchell representatives was less than forthcoming stating only that "Mitchell has invested significant resources and technical expertise in the development of this new BattleMech."</p>]]></desc>
		<service>TNN</service>
		<location>Terra</location>
	</newsItem>
<!-- Succession Wars Era (2781 - 3049) -->
	<!-- Early Succession Wars (2781 - 2900) -->
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Factories destroyed on Caph, General Systems in trouble</headline><!-- Source: Technical Readout: 3050 Upgrade -->
		<date>2793</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The General Systems factories on Caph are the latest casualties of the ongoing hostilities gripping the Inner Sphere. Material losses are reported to be catastrophic while the human cost is currently being calculated. Forces from several Successor States were involved in a battle that leveled the production facility and the surrounding areas. Bombardments from all sides have turned several populated areas into ruins over the last few months. Capellan forces have since taken the remaining facilities. This facility was the only producer of the <em>Exterminator</em> BattleMech in the Inner Sphere.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>FNS</service>
		<location>Caph</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Mercury refits for longer life</headline><!-- Source: Technical Readout: 2750 -->
		<date>2810</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The <em>Mercury</em> BattleMech, a staple design since 2742 has been the most recent candidate for refits based on the increasing rarity of the original parts. Several systems have been replaced to more common models which has allowed the <em>MCY-98</em> to increase its armor protection. Unfortunately, these downgrades are removing some of the most prominent features of the speedy 'Mech and leaves pilots relying on that additional protection from enemies they would normally out run."</p>]]></desc>
		<service>TNN</service>
		<location>Terra</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Grand Championship ends, Champion MechWarrior crowned</headline><!-- Source: Solaris VII Box Set (No canon date) -->
		<date>2812-04</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The Solaris VII Grand Championships have come to an end with only Cabol Hirsch standing. After months of grueling matches, the final four MechWarriors brought the Games to a close with explosive results. Several competitors this year had the skills to take the top honor but fell just short as several technical issues plagued Stables. Many owners are calling for investigations as many of the more serious cases involved equipment malfunctions during or prior to matches.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>SBC</service>
		<location>Solaris VII</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Planetary disaster strikes Lone Star</headline><!-- Source: Touring the Stars: Lone Star -->
		<date>2825</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The most recent casualty of the Succession Wars has just made its mark on the planet Lone Star. The moon, Vespa, entered the atmosphere earlier this week with devastating results. While it is unclear at this time how many injuries there are, this event will change the face of the planet for generations to come.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>SBC</service>
		<location>Lone Star</location>
	</newsItem> 
	<newsItem><!-- ISSUE - Rewording required -->
		<headline>Marik forces destroyed after fleeing Solaris</headline><!-- Source: Solaris: The Reaches -->
		<date>2903-05</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Filed 02 April 2903</p><p>There is muted celebration on Solaris VII today as the war criminals from the Free Worlds League were immediately and irrevocably destroyed during a failed jump out of the system. The ship, <em>Despiser</em>, opened fire on the world with nuclear weapons before attempting to flee. A failed jump resulted in the destroyer breaking up above the planet in an incredible display of light. While there is no current accounting of casualties, the areas around Xolara are currently being treated as a hazardous zone and all emergency personnel responding to the incident are required to have the maximum level of protective gear.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CBN</service>
		<location>Solaris VII</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Ruins to hold classes once again</headline><!-- Source: Field Manual: Draconis Combine -->
		<date>2910</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Reconstruction has completed on a facility almost entirely destroyed in 2865. The rebuilt facility, now named the Dover Institute of Higher Learning, is slated to begin its first classes later this year. The Dover Institute of Higher Learning is to be a centre of learning and training to ensure the Combine is ready for the years to come, home to a technician school, an engineering school, a medical school, and even a small but elite MechWarrior training program. The curriculum is anticipated to be extremely intense, to produce elite graduates for the glory of the Draconis Combine.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CBN</service>
		<location>Ashio</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Parliament seeks restitution from First Lord and Captain-General</headline><!-- Source: House Marik (The Free Worlds League) -->
		<date>2989-10</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Filed 12 September 2989</p><p>Parliament is setting a new precident by demanding restitution from the First Lord and Captain-General and the military as a whole to replenish funds used during the recent wars. Special Resolution 512 calls for funds, materials, and equipment to be disbursed back into the FWL economy to help bolster those industries most effected by the fighting. No official word from the office of the First Lord. Economists are following this news intently as these reparations could significantly bolster struggling economies across the FWL.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>ABC</service>
		<location>Atreus</location>
	</newsItem>
	<!-- Late Succession Wars (2901 - 3049) -->
	<newsItem>
		<headline>New Commander of the Otomo</headline><!-- Source: House Kurita (The Draconis Combine) -->
		<date>3000-02</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Filed 01 January 3000</p><p>Takashi Kurita has served with honor and distinction with the Second Sword of Light. For his service, the Coordinator has promoted Kurita Takashi-sama to the rank of <em>sho-sho</em> and named his voice in High Command of the Arm of the Dragon. The Coordinator further showed his trust of Kurita Takashi-sama by naming him commander of the <em>Otomo</em>, charged with the safety of the Imperial Place here on Luthien.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>VotD</service>
		<location>Luthien</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Kalidasa's 'Mech Factory Assaulted</headline><!-- Source: TBD -->
		<date>3000-02</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Filed 23 January 3000</p><p>In a daring raid, persons unknown attacked Kalidasa’s 'Mech Factory today. The attackers struck before dawn with unknown intent, however attempts to steal BattleMechs coming off the production line failed when security forces overran the primary hostile force.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Kalidasa</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Hesperus II under attack</headline><!-- Source: House Steiner (The Lyran Commonwealth) --><!-- No canon date -->
		<date>3000-04-02</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Filed 28 March 3000</p><p>Three days ago, House Kurita was able to push through the aerospace coverage of Hesperus II and land one BattleMech regiment and its support elements. Since that time, they have made periodic raids of defenders here on the starport hoping to push the ELH out...<em>*muffled scream from off-camera* "INCOMING"</em>... of the starport leaving the way for more Kurita reinforcements, that we hear are inbound. This is Sylvia Denzel for <em>*explosions rips through the concourse where the reporter is*</em></p>]]></desc>
		<service>TBC</service>
		<location>Hesperus II</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Federated Suns raids Kalidasa</headline><!-- Source: TBD -->
		<date>3000-06</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Filed 18 April 3000</p><p>In a daring raid, the Federated Suns has raided Kalidasa earlier in the month. In a running battle between planetary militia forces and the raiders supplies earmarked for the defense of the front against House Steiner have disappeared. There are rumors that this open attack with easily identified forces is to accomplish what the Federated Suns was unable to accomplish by subterfuge earlier this year.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Kalidasa</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Suzano lost to Capellan Confederation... Recovered</headline><!-- Source: Technical Readout: 3026, Revised -->
		<date>3000</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Suzano, long a world held by the Free World League and frequently raided by the Capellan Confederation, was "raided" in early June of this year. However, this time because House Marik had stripped our defenders away, the CCAF raiding forces that scouting our world were able to conquered it. It was thanks to the Third and Fifth Mechanized Infantry Companies that their reign was only three months long. However the damage they inflicted on the League's population will be years in the recovery.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>IMI</service>
		<location>Suzano</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Eridani Light Horse speaks out</headline><!-- Source: TBD -->
		<date>3000</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Eridani Light Horse in a public statement today, announced that they were leaving the Lyran Commonwealth for the Federated Suns. They stated that those "incompetent social generals" that they were assigned under had led the Light Horse to too many casualties to be tolerated in command of such elite soldiers.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Tharkad</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Astrokaszy stablizes under new Caliph</headline><!-- Source: The Periphery -->
		<date>3001</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>ComStar has announced that a new ruler of the Periphery world Astrokaszy. Caliph Omar Shervanis stands ready to join the galaxy community after uniting the various people of the world Astrokaszy. To cement this new addition, Comstar has announced the building of a Class B HPG on world.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Astrokaszy</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Warrior Houses defeat 7th Crucis Lancers</headline><!-- Source: House Davion (The Federated Suns) -->
		<date>3001</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>It is with great pride to announce today that the Blessed Orders of the Warrior Houses Imarra and LuSann have fought the 7th Crucis Lancers of that hated Federated Suns to a standstill then forced them off Lincoln.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CBS</service>
		<location>Lincoln</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>New cargo transport released by Lockheed and CBM Industries</headline><!-- Source: MUL Online -->
		<date>3001</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Lockheed and CBM Industries have announced the release of a new heavy cargo transport in a joint press conference. The press conference lasted over an hour as several concerns were addressed as to the similarity of the new vehicle, the <em>KC-5</em>, and its resemblance to the <em>Karnov</em> VTOL already being produced by NETC. Reporters are allegedly referring to this new vehicle as the <em>King Karnov</em>.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>DBC</service>
		<location>Gibbs</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Quickdraw variant unveiled by Technicron Manufacturing</headline><!-- Source: Technical Readout: 3025 -->
		<date>3002</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>In response to the limited effectiveness of the <em>Quickdraw QKD-4G</em>, Technicron Manufacturing has released the technical specification for their new variant the <em>QKD-5A</em>. This new model replaces the Delta Dart LRMs with additional medium lasers and heat sinks. This limits the stand-off distances that many pilots used to soften their targets but allows for longivity in the field with ammo independence. Stocks have had a slight jump for Technicron and Fusigon Heavy Weaponry, the provider of the additional lasers. Limited runs of this variant will be made available but field refit kits will make up the bulk of anticipated sales.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>ABC</service>
		<location>Savannah</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Anton Marik titled Duke of Procyon</headline><!-- Source: House Marik (The Free Worlds League) -->
		<date>3002</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Anton Marik, General in the FWLM, was presented with the title of Duke of Procyon today. He is expected to take command of the Capellan Front soon.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>IMI</service>
		<location>Procyon</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>House Kurita honors lost son</headline><!-- Source: House Kurita (The Draconis Combine) --><!-- Noncanon Location -->
		<date>3002-03</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Voice of the Dragon has the duty of reporting the fall of Miyamoto Kurita in the battle for Cylene II.</p><p><em>Note: the location is not canonical</em></p>]]></desc>
		<service>Voice of the Dragon</service>
		<location>Luthien</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Loric Attacked</headline><!-- Source: Historical: Brush Wars -->
		<date>3002-05</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Filed 3002-04-16</p><p>Free World League soldiers forced their way onto our peaceful planet earlier this month. However, the recently arrived 17th Donegal Guards, who joined our defenders earlier this year, proved their worth by forcing House Marik to fight for every inch of soil of our paradise.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>TBC</service>
		<location>Loric</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Davion forces trapped on Cammal</headline><!-- Source: TBD -->
		<date>3002-07</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Filed 3002-06-16</p><p>In a display of strategic maneuvering today, Warrior House Ijori of the Capellen Confederation was able to spring a trap on Davion forces. Will this spell the chance the CC needs to take over this world? Keep tuned to FSNN for the latest and most accurate news affecting you.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>FSNN</service>
		<location>Cammal</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Gordon's Highland Light Captured</headline><!-- Source: House Liao (The Capellan Confederation) -->
		<date>3002</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>In a fast tempo recon raid, the 2nd St Ives Lancers were able to outmaneuver and capture the Gordon's Highland Light mercenary company intact. Look forward to facing twelve <em>Panthers</em> next time you accidently are facing the St Ives Lancers in combat.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>MercNet</service>
		<location>Pinard</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Gorton, Kingsley and Thorpe Release MechBuster Fighter</headline><!-- Source: TBD --><!-- Original Note: added MechBuster per Sarna date -->
		<date>3002</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[In a press conference today on Rasalhague, representatives of GK&T presented the first public view of the MechBuster conventional fighter, an airframe devoted to devastating ground attack. It is armed with the Zeus 75 Autocannon/20, which fires a four-round burst of hyper-velocity depleted uranium armor penetrators. <p>Presented for procurement to the Draconis Combine Mustered Soldiery, the MechBuster is sure to make its presence known to the Dragon's enemies.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>Voice of the Dragon</service>
		<location>Rasalhague</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>ISF Report: Akiro Kurita</headline><!--  Source: TBD --><!-- Classified data? -->
		<date>3002-09-30</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[Filed 3002-09-30<p>Assistant Director Subhash Indrahar,<br>At your request we have probed deeper into the patrol that claimed Akiro Kurita's life on 09-04-3002. The investigation, which raised no outliers on the first look but on second pass, uncovered a long buried report regarding the <em>Sholagar</em> aerospace fighter, which Kurita Akiro-sama was piloting on that day. In 2989, during the Battle of Severn, a lance of <em>Sholagar</em> fighters followed an aerospace unit into atmospheric conditions that interfered with the operational profile of the <em>Sholagar</em>. We have also found additional evidence in the technical reports we have acquired from the Capellan Confederation regarding their <em>Thrush</em> aerospace fighter, which has the same operational profile as our <em>Sholagar</em>.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>ISF</service>
		<location>Luthien</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Solaris VII offers to FWL a place in the games</headline><!-- Source:  Historical: Brush Wars -->
		<date>3002-10</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>This is Ilias Albert for Solaris 7 News. Earlier this month, General Willis Crawford burned hard to land his forces on the Gaming World. The Defenders of Solaris, the LCAF, with advanced warning of his assault were able to gather the numerous volunteers who offered their services to the LCAF to oppose his landing to the Gaming World. The landing was a bloodbath for the FWL. After escaping circlement his forces were able to push back the forces opposing him and secure a stronghold. We at Solaris 7 News say, "Let the games continue!"</p>]]></desc>
		<service>S7NN</service>
		<location>Solaris VII</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Solaris VII Games continue under Lyran control</headline><!-- Source: Historical: Brush Wars -->
		<date>3002-12</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[Filed 3002-11-20<p>This is Solaris 7 News and I am Kalina Križ. Today it has been confirmed that the invading Marik forces under General Willis Crawford have been defeated. The furious counterattack by the Donegal Guards started with a strafing run by some of the few <em>Seydlitz</em> left in service, leaving the FWLM woefully short of aerospace fighters to counter LCAF air supremacy. Moreover, the operational tempo did not let up until half of the general's command was stretched over a salvage-covered wasteland. General Crawford retreated with what is left of his command off world. We at S7NN welcome the Donegal Guards and hope they enjoy the Games while on Solaris 7.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>S7NN</service>
		<location>Solaris VII</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Death Commandos to take new recruits</headline><!-- Source: Field Manual: Capellan Confederation -->
		<date>3003</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The Chancellor announced today that the cream of CCAF would be given the chance to advance further in the cause of the Confederation by joining the Death Commandos.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CBS</service>
		<location>Capalla</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Mercenaries captured on Tsumma</headline><!-- Source: House Davion (The Federated Suns) -->
		<date>3003</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>MercNet has received reports that the Dry River Devils, a Davion-employed mercenary unit, was captured by the Warrior House Ijori of the Capellan Confederation. We at MercNet are curious about a CCAF unit being so far inside the Federated Suns. We will continue providing future updates on this issue.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>MercNet</service>
		<location>Tsumma</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>General Willis Crawford Court-Martialed and Executed</headline><!-- Source: Historical: Brush Wars -->
		<date>3003-07</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[Filed 3003-06-01<p>A FWLM representative has announced a new chapter in the series of events relating to the 3002 invasion of Solaris VII by the FWL today. General Willis Crawford, who was arrested in December of 3002, finally got his time in front of a military court regarding his handling of the invasion. The court announced today that General Willis Crawford was found guilty in a general court-martial of misbehavior before the enemy along with lesser-included offences. He was stripped of rank and executed by firing squad this afternoon. He is the first military officer in the FWL to be executed in over a century.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>IMI</service>
		<location>Atrus</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Michael Hasek marries Marie Davion</headline><!-- Source: House Davion (The Federated Suns) -->
		<date>3003-09</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[Filed 3003-08-02<p>Michael Hasek married Marie Davion in a beautiful ceremony in the beginning of August. Michael Hasek-Davion, formally combining his name with his wife's, the son of George Hasek, Duke of New Syrtis and a former officer in the Syrtis Fusiliers brigade of the AFFS. Marie Davion is the daughter of First Prince Andrew Davion and Simon St. Clair.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>FSNN</service>
		<location>New Syrtis</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Blantleff, a possible Kentares IV?</headline><!-- Source: The Periphery, 1st Edition -->
		<date>3003-10</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[Filed 3003-06-02<p>Lothian League informed Comstar News Bureau of an attempted massacre of Lothian settlers on the world of Blantleff. The Circinus Federation, which has lived peacefully with the Lothian settlers for more than a decade, decided stake their claim the small world. However, through the actions of an educated man the Lothian settlers were able to survive long enough for help to arrive. President H. R. "Little Bob" McIntyre of the Circinus Federation had no comment at time of posting.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Blanetleff</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Hohiro Kurita Assassinated</headline><!-- Source: Heir to the Dragon -->
		<date>3004-02-04</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[Filed 3004-02-03<p>In a stunning annnoucement today from the Imperial Palace on Luthien, Coordinator Hohiro Kurita was assassinated by a Otomo Kashira. Coordinator Takashi Kurita, who was Commander of the Otomo, has taken over as Head of House Kurita and title of Coordinator of the Draconis Combine.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Luthien</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Captain-General addresses Parliament, promises victory</headline><!-- Source: House Marik (The Free Worlds League) -->
		<date>3004-03</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Captain-General Janos Marik spoke to the Parliament in Feburary, promising victory over the "barbarians" who are destroying humanity. His speech was directed at the Lyran Commonwealth and other Successor States who prey upon their neighbors. His words, while overwhelmingly positive in describing the FWLM capabilities, fell on a room of politicians largely concerned with maintaining the profitability of the FWL. </p>]]></desc>
		<service>INI</service>
		<location>Atreus</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>ComStar Adepts Killed in Massacres on Lost and Canal</headline>
		<date>3004</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[ComStar News Bureau can now confirm reports from the worlds of Lost and Canal that murderious raiders from beyond the Lyran border have struck HPG compounds on both worlds. While the Blessed Order has declined to comment on what may have driven these attacks, they stress that rebuilding the two HPGs remains the Order's top priority, and renewed calls for the Lyran Commonwealth Armed Forces to take a heavier hand in policing the nearby worlds.]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Quanatir</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Summer raided by DCMS</headline><!-- Source House Steiner (The Lyran Commonwealth) -->
		<date>3005-04</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[Filed 3005-03-20<p>House Kurita in response to raids of the LCAF raided Summer yesterday. Thanks to the lucky positioning of members of the 3rd Royal Guard, the raid on the palace of the Duke of Summer was repulsed. However, they were unable to prevent all casaulties, the Duke has died and his heir-appearant is currently in critical condition.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>TBC</service>
		<location>Summer</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Indicass raided by Federated Suns</headline><!-- Source: House Liao (The Capellan Confederation) -->
		<date>3005-06</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[Filed 3005-04-27<p>The Ceti Hussars of the AFFS deployed to Indicass in a quick raid. However, they did not count on Cochraine's Goliaths and turned a raid into a retreat. Two companies of the enemy never left Indicass.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CBS</service>
		<location>Indicass</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>New Mercenary Brigade arrives at Delos IV</headline><!-- Source: Wolf's Dragoons -->
		<date>3005-05</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[Filed 3005-04-11<p>A surprise that no world would welcome happened in the Delos IV system. Jumping in was not one or two JumpShips but 7+ JumpShips all loaded for bear with military DropShips. To further add to the surprise was a message stating simply "I am Colonal Jamie Wolf, I come in peace."</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Delos IV</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Kittery absorbed into Federated Suns</headline><!-- Source: Classic BattleTech Companion -->
		<date>3005-10</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Filed 35 September 3005</p><p>While the Ceti Hussars were raiding Indicass, another battle was being fought on Kittery. A heavy assault force landed and secured the world for the Federated Suns. However, with the current unhappiness the military governor has a long road ahead of them for the hearts and minds of Kittery's populace.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>FSNN</service>
		<location>Kittery</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Alessandro Steiner abdicates in favor of Katrina</headline>
		<date>3007-07-22</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[Archon Alessandro Steiner today abdicated the throne of the Lyran Commonwealth to his relative, Katrina Steiner.<p>This move comes after a series of defeats, both political and military, for the aging Archon. Katrina Steiner, a veteran of the LCAF and a hero of the battles of Hesperus II, is expected to reverse many of the Archon's most ill-favored policies and bring stability to the realm.</p> ]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Tharkad</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>House Davion, Mercenaries Attack New Aragon</headline>
		<date>3008-03-30</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[Yesterday ten BattleMech regiments, along with more than twice that in conventional forces, from the Federated Suns attacked the Capellan world of New Aragon. The Capellan Confederation Armed Forces, long expecting the attack, had already gathered eight BattleMech regiments to repulse them.<p>Half the Suns forces are the elite and mysterious Wolf's Dragoons mercenaries who have made such a name for themselves along the Capellan border for the last several years. The Dragoons, who have founded what seems a feud with the Capellan-employed mercenaries known as McCarron's Armored Cavarly, are heavily involved in the initial attacks.</p><p>Speaking from New Avalon, First Prince Ian Davion cheered the no-doubt coordinated assault, calling New Aragon "the crown jewel of the Sarna Commonality" and a keystone in the Capellan defense strategy.</p><p>Capellan military spokespersons have refused comment, but the fact that our Blessed Order's representatives were able to speak to Crucis Lancer officers on-planet certainly suggest the Davion landings were successful.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>New Aragon</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Wolf's Dragoons Vanish</headline>
		<date>3009-01-11</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[AFFS spokespeople confirmed today that the bulk of Wolf's Dragoons has left the New Valencia system, but would not confirm or deny they knew the mercenaries' destination. The few Dragoons left on-planet also refused to comment on their comrades' intentions, only saying it was an approved movement order.<p>It is not unusual for almost all of the Dragoons to be off of New Valencia. Just last year, before the spectacular assault on New Aragon, almost all the combat elements left. But what is unusual this time is that almost the enture support apparatus the insular Dragoons have maintained is gone with them this time. The streets and halls of Fort Jaime are deserted.</p><p>Federated Suns News Service spole with one AFFS officer, who refused to be identified, who claims the Dragoons are off on a long strike against another powerful Capellan target, perhaps Sarna itself, or even Sian. Our military consultants say that is unlikely, given the mauling the Dragoons suffered on New Aragon, but possible.</p><p>A more likely scenario is simple: wherever the Dragoons first got their windfall of 'Mechs, tanks and more, they didn't use it all. And they've gone back for more.</p><p>That's an idea this reporter can't wait to see played out.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>FSNS</service>
		<location>New Valencia</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>First Prince targets New Aragon</headline><!-- Source: Wolf's Dragoons -->
		<date>3008-04</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[Filed 3008-03-29<p>First Prince Ian Davion discussed the intent for a new campaign in the Sarna March during a speech today. While some analysts wonder why he named the palnet ahead of any invasion, it has some thinking that this is a diversion intending to draw forces away from other worlds. New Aragon, within the borders of the Capellan Confederation, is an agricultural world that has several innovative medical facilities.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>FIB</service>
		<location>New Avalon</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Archon married</headline><!-- Source: The Kell Hounds Scenario Pack -->
		<date>3009-03-18</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>According to officials on Tharkad, Archon Katrina Steiner married long-time lover and Duke of Donegal Arthur Luvon less than a week ago. The Lyran Commonwealth is celebrating the wedding of their beloved Archon. Archon Steiner and Duke Luvon have been romantically linked since at least 3005 - hopefully the marriage of the two will produce an heir and quiet some of the current pretenders to the Lyran throne. That is all for our Commonwealth Update - back to local news.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Tharkad</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Dragoons New Mystery 'Mech</headline>
		<date>3009-12-22</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[When the Wolf's Dragoons returned to New Valencia in 3009 they returned with more new, pristine war machines that no one had seen in centuries. Or in sevearal cases, ever before.<p>One such case is a massive, slow assault 'Mech we've heard is called an <em>Annihilator</em>. This beast stumps around with no hands and four deadly autocannons, each of them equal to the guns carried by Davion <em>Enforcer</em> or <em>Centurion</em> BattleMechs. None of the Dragoons are willing to tell us where these and other 'Mech came from, where they were built, or how many more of them there might be.</p><p>Once again, the mysterious Dragoons pose more questions than they can answer.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>FSNS</service>
		<location>New Valencia</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Heir to the Throne</headline><!-- Source: Era Report: 3052 -->
		<date>3010-02-27</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The Lyran Commonwealth is celebrating the birth of the new heir to the nation's throne. Archon Katrina was reported to have given birth earlier this month and today officials at the Triad finally confirmed it. They also added that mother and daughter are doing well. The entire Commonwealth welcomes Melissa Steiner and we at Tharkad Broadcasting hope for a bright future for her.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>TBC</service>
		<location>Tharkad</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Merlin's debut</headline><!-- Source: MUL Online -->
		<date>3010-05-15</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The military community was shocked earlier this month to learn that the Mountain Wolf BattleMechs (MWBM) factory on Alpheratz was rebuilt in secret by the Outworld's Alliance and just recently produced its first new BattleMech. Even more surprising was the news that the 'Mech was of a brand new design, dubbed the <em>Merlin</em> by MWBM, it is a sturdy heavy 'Mech that uses parts common throughout the Inner Sphere and Periphery. The news of a new 'Mech has the military community quite excited as this is the first entirely new design in over 100 years. MWBM is reported to already have a line of customers interested in pruchasing the new 'Mechs just as quickly as they can make them.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Alpheratz</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Obituary: Duke Arthur Luvon</headline><!-- Source: A Clever Bit of Fiction -->
		<date>3010-06-05</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>It is a sad day for the Commonwealth and especially Archon Katrina and her infant daughter Melissa - we have just received an official report that Arthur Luvon, Duke of Donegal, husband to Archon Katrina, and father to Melissa, passed away yesterday. Duke Luvon has reportedly been battling cancer for some time now. Those of us here at Donegal Broadcasting were deeply saddened by the loss of our Duke and our condolences go out to the royal family.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>DBC</service>
		<location>Donegal</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>8th Galedon Regulars formed</headline><!-- Source: The Galtor Campaign -->
		<date>3011-03-19</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>There are reports of heightened security throughout the Federated Sun's Draconis March after news leaked that the Draconis Combine recently reformed the 8th Galedon Regulars. While there is very little known about the newly reformed regiment, reports indicate the unit is comprised primarily of heavy and assault 'Mechs. While one regiment is unlikely to make an impact on the highly contested border, the addition of a new assault regiment is never welcome news.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>FSNS</service>
		<location>Robinson</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Hell's Black Aces formed</headline><!-- Source: Field Manual: Mercenaries (Revised) -->
		<date>3011-05-23</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>In mercenary news, a new aerospace unit has shown up on Galatea looking for work. So far unnamed, these Capellan ex-pats recently defected from the Capellan Confederation citing long term neglect by the CCAF and fear of Chancellor Maximilian's regular “purges” of the military. The new mercenaries made off with their entire Wing of fighters, support personnel, and even a rare <em>Vengeance<em>-class DropShip. They are currently looking for high risk contracts for either a major house or under another mercenary unit to provide aerospace fighter support.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Galatea</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Hanse Davion awarded command of 3rd Davion Guards</headline><!-- Source: House Davion (The Federated Suns) -->
		<date>3011-06-27</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Earlier this month Heir-Apparent Hanse Davion was awarded full command of the illustrious 3rd Davion Guards. Hanse has been an officier in the 3rd Davion ever since he graduated with honors from the Albion Military Academy and has proven to be an exceptional officer. His graduation ranking rated him for a spot as a lieutenant and he has steadily worked his way up the chain of command due to his success on the field.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>NANS</service>
		<location>New Avalon</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>2nd Winfield's Guards destroyed</headline><!-- Source: Technical Readout: 3025 (Revised) -->
		<date>3011-11-22</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Breaking news from Sevren, after a determined assault by Combine forces, the Commonwealth defenders managed to drive off the attack, however losses were heavy. The 2nd Winfield Guards were decimated and reports indicate that the unit is completely combat ineffective and survivors will be rolled into the 1st Winfield Guards, which also suffered heavy damage. This battle represents yet another major failure by the Commonwealth's intelligence community for failing to note the relocation of such a large Combine force. If the 1st Guards had not arrived from Laurent when they did it is likely the planet Sevren would now belong to the Combine and all members of the 2nd Guards captured or killed.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CP</service>
		<location>Winfield</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Hanse Davion named Governor of New Aragon</headline><!-- Source: Dark Age: Republic Worlds (3130) -->
		<date>3012-03-22</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Today Hanse Davion, heir to the Federated Suns, was promoted to Field Marshal of the Capellan March, giving him command over all AFFS units along the Confederation border. This latest promotion is just one of many in Hanse's meteoric rise in power in recent years. He has worked his way from lance commander in the 3rd Davion Guards to ultimately become the CO of the entire famed regiment barely a year ago and then barely a month ago he was appointed Military Governor of newly liberated New Aragon. The latest promotion for Hanse makes him one of the most powerful men in the Suns and is a show of great faith from his older brother, First Prince Ian Davion.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>FSNS</service>
		<location>New Aragon</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Hendrik Grimm III founds Oberon Confederation</headline><!-- Source: The Periphery (2nd Edition) -->
		<date>3012-06-05</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>In a surprising turn of events, self-styled King, Hendrik Grimm III has declared the founding of the Oberon Confederation, with a power base consisting of his large pirate band that has existed since at least 2855 when his grandfather, Hendrik Grimm, deserted from the LCAF along with many of the soldiers that served under him. The unit turned to piracy and made Oberon VI their base of operations and they have been plaguing surrounding system for more than a century.</p><p>Oberon VI was once a jewel of the Rim Worlds Republic in the days of the Star League but never recovered from the ravages of the Amaris Coup. A century after the fall of the Star League the planet made for an easy target for the original Hendrik Grimm and a pirate's haven was founded and slavery became rampant.</p><p>King Grimm III has promised social and political reform and a change to his ways, including using his men and 'Mechs to defend his new Confederation and to take on legitimate mercenary work for units that can be spared. What will actually become of the new nation remains to be seen. When asked for comment Lyran officials refused to make any public comments, though a few annonymously condemned Hendrik Grimm III and his "pirate nation".</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Oberon VI</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Captain-General MIA?</headline><!-- Source: Wolf's Dragoon Sourcebook -->
		<date>3012-09-15</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Shocking news from Atreus. Following the death of the Captain-General's second wife, Ana Stewart, and two of their children earlier this year, sources in the Captain-General's offices say that Janos Marik has completely withdrawn from the public eye and sees only a very select few people and otherwise has barely ventured from his personal suite. While various news outlets have noted the lack of public appearances by the Captain-General no one knew just how far withdrawn Janos Marik had become. What will this mean for the League if the Captain-General is absent and can he adequately lead from behind closed doors? We ask our panel of experts.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>SFP</service>
		<location>Stewart</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Kyalla Centrella Named Magestrix</headline>
		<date>3012</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[The people of the Magistracy of Canopus, a nation in the Periphery off the Free Worlds League, have named Kyalla Centrella Magestrix and ruler after the death of her mother. Few observers were surprised by this, as Centrellas have always ruled the Magistracy, though pundits are already beginning to question some of the Magestrix's new policies. She seems too interested in what she receives, they say, and not intersted enough in her duties.]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Canopus IV</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Marauder II unveiled</headline><!-- Source: MUL Online -->
		<date>3012-11-05</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Today, representatives of a joint General Motors and Blackwell Industries unveiled the <em>Marauder II</em>, a fiercesome 100-ton assault 'Mech. While the new 'Mech is 33% heavier than the original, the 'Mech has a lot in common with its lighter sire, pairing a PPC and laser in each arm, with a large laser in place of the traditional autocannon. While the new <em>Marauder II</em> is slower, engineers have compensated by adding jump jets that allow this 'Mech to jump up to 90 meters at a time. The initial line of <em>Marauder II</em>s are slated for the Wolf's Dragoons, however Blackwell representatives stated that they would begin taking orders on a first-come, first-serve basis starting in six-months.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Galatea</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Artillery Cannons Enter Production</headline>
		<date>3012</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[In what may have been the most unattended press conference in recent years, engineers from Defiance Industries' weaponry division announced production models of three classes of artillery cannons had been completed and were ready for order. When pressed, they admitted no orders had yet been recieved.<p>The cannons, variants of the venerable Long Tom, Sniper and Thumper artillery pieces, were described as "sawed-off assault guns" by one engineer. She went on to add "Artillery is great for shooting things you can't see, but sometimes our troops need do be able to point an enemy strongpoint and say 'see that whole area over there? I need it taken care of,' and our new guns do that."</p><p>Hesperus procurement representatives were present, but none we spoke with would admit to any existing orders.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>TBC</service>
		<location>Hesperus II</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Wolf's Dragoons on Carver V?</headline><!-- Source: Mercenary Handbook: 3055 -->
		<date>3013-03-09</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>CNB has received reports from Carver V that the mysterious Wolf's Dragoons mercenary unit has been spotted on the Capellan Confederation planet. While Capellan officials refuse to comment, stating that they can "never discuss military deployments due to security concerns" rumors abound that the infamous mercenary unit has been deployed to garrison Carver V. If true, it would explain the lack of action from the Dragoons in recent months, though it does not take a military analyst to question why such a powerful unit would be withheld from combat.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Galatea</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Obituary: Herodias Ap Gwynn</headline><!-- Source: The Periphery Sourcebook -->
		<date>3013-04-12</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>It is with great remorse that I bring you the following report. Herodias Ap Gwynn, the founder of the Pan-Humanist doctrine, was found dead earlier today.</p><p>Herodias Ap Gwynn was well respected throughout the Alliance as an idealist, pacifist and philosopher, whose idea attracted hundreds if not thousands of followers to his view that humantiy shares a common path and goal. He spent his life as a conciliator, diplomat and techer, instructing his followers to offer aid to those in need and to spread peace, education and medicine throughout the known galaxy.</p><p>Herodias Ap Gwynn was 60 years old, at this time the cause of death is unknown, though authorities do not suspect foul-play was involved. Ceremonies will be held on Alpheratz in two weeks, with hundreds of Pan Humanists expected to be in attendance.</p><p>Officials from the organization that Herodias Ap Gwynn began decades ago promised that his works and teachings will continue even after his death.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>OAB</service>
		<location>Alpheratz</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>12th Star Guards, longtime LCAF mercenaries, head for Davion Space</headline>
		<date>3013</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Representatives of the 12th Star Guards confirmed today that the longtime Steiner mercenaries have negotiated a new contract with the Federated Suns following the embezzelling scandal discovered earlier this year.</p><p>MercNet has not been able to get comment from the LCAF about how they will replace the 4-regiment gap in their defenses when the Star Guards depart, but one thing is sure: few single units can replace the Star Guards, so we expect to see the Commonwealth offering top rates for a lot of mercenaries in the next few years.]]></desc>
		<service>MercNet</service>
		<location>Galatea</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Kell Hounds stop Combine incursion</headline><!-- Source: The Kell Hounds -->
		<date>3013-05-18</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Reports have finally been cleared by the AFFS that a raid on the planet Mara by the 9th Sun Zhang Academy Cadre was thwarted by the Kell Hounds mercenary regiment. Not only did the Kell Hounds manage to defeat the Cadre unit, they also captured their JumpShips, stranding 9th Cadre in the system until the Draconis Combine was able to pay reparations for the raid.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>NANS</service>
		<location>Mara</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Obituary: Duke George Hasek</headline><!-- Source: House Davion (The Federated Suns) -->
		<date>3013-05-30</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>We received word today that Duke George Hasek died in his sleep early this morning. The Capellan March and the Federated Suns as a whole are in mourning today after the loss of this great leader. Duke Hasek dedicated his life to bettering the planets of the Capellan March and the people living on thos planets, his loss will not soon be forgotten. Memorial and burial services will be held later this week.</p><p>In addition, the ceremony to name the new Duke of New Syrtis is planned for following week. Duke George Hasek's son, Michael Hasek-Davion, will become the new Duke of New Syrtis and Field Marshal of the Capellan March. Michael Hasek-Davion has many years of experience assisting his father in running the March.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>NSN</service>
		<location>New Syrtis</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Candace Liao spotted with Colonel Jamie Wolf</headline><!-- Source: Wolf's Dragoons Sourcebook -->
		<date>3013-06-01</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Lurid news from the Capellan Confederation; unconfirmed rumors place Duchess Candance Liao on the planet of Carver V with the Wolf's Dragoons mercenaries and suggest that the Duchess is trying to attract Colonel Jamie Wolf himself. Anonymous witnesses from the Confederation report that Candace Liao has used her position as Duchess to gain access to the famous mercenary and has been less than subtle with her intent to begin a relationship with the commander of the infamous Dragoons. Reports indicate that so far Jamie Wolf has turned down all requests from the heir to the Confederation.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>ISI</service>
		<location>Carver V</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Federated Suns in mourning</headline><!-- Source: House Kurita (The Draconis Combine) -->
		<date>3013-10-22</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The Federated Suns is in mourning today with the arrival of news that First Prince Ian Davion was killed yesterday while fighting on Mallory's World. Davion forces, led by General Eugene Drivers and his 17th Avalon Hussars and the local militia held off the larger Combine forces consisting of the elite 2nd Sword of Light and the 24th Dieron Regulars for 11 days before First Prince Ian Davion arrived with the 4th Davion Guards.</p><p>Within a week of landing on Mallory's World, the First Prince and the 4th Guards broke the Combine's siege of Colterville, where they had the Hussars pinned. The First Prince then pushed the Davion Guards to break the 2nd Sword of Light, ordering the Hussars to guard his flank and keep the 24th at bay. Unfortunately, disaster struck with the 17th attempted an orbital drop, a specialty of the unit, on the numerical superior 24th Dieron Regulars and the 17th Hussars were crushed. The survivors fled back to Colterville and the 4th Davion Guard's flank was left unprotected.</p><p>The Guards quickly found themselves surrounded, however the First Prince managed to spend more than a week evading the trap before the Guards were bottlenecked at the Desolation Pass canyons on October 21st and could no longer keep ahead of their pursuers. The fighting was brutal and the 4th Davion Guards were soon forced to pull further into the canyons. First Prince Ian Davion elected to act as rear-guard for his battered soldiers where he ultimately fell in battle.</p><p>The Kell Hounds mercenaries, sent to rescue the Prince, made it to Desolation Pass moments too late to save the First Prince but they were able to drive off the 2nd Sword of Light.</p><p>As the late First Prince's heir, Hanse Davion was crowned First Prince of the Federated Suns during a hasty ceremony on New Avalon earlier today. The new First Prince named Yvonne Davion as his Champion.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>FSNS</service>
		<location>New Avalon</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>1st Federated Suns Armored Cavalry christened</headline><!-- Source: TBD -->
		<date>3013-12-31</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>3013 proved to be a tragic year as the Federated Suns saw the death of both First Prince Ian Davion, killed in action on Mallory's World, and Duke George Hasek, lord of the Capellan March, who died in his sleep. The leadership and guidance both men provided will be greatly missed but today, the Federated Suns looks towards a brighter 3014 as this year draws to a close.</p><p>In a ceremony honoring his brother, First Prince Hanse Davion christened the 1st Federated Suns Armored Cavalry. The new regiment will be based on Ziliang and is a medium-weight unit with a strong focus on mobility and firepower. The First Prince hand selected some of the top MechWarriors and aerospace pilots from across the realm to undertake his grand experiment.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>NANS</service>
		<location>Ziliang</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Battle for Halstead Station</headline><!-- Source: Handbook: House Davion -->
		<date>3014-01-06</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>CNB has received an exclusive report that the Federated Suns' First Prince Hanse Davion recently launched a massive invasion of the Draconis Combine planet Halstead Station. Our confidential source indicated that the invasion was authorized by the First Prince himself after MIIO uncovered reports of a massive LosTech warehouse somewhere on the planet. Without a doubt, the First Prince is hoping to capture the planet so that this technology can be claimed by the Suns.</p><p>News from the planet seems to be cut off, however we have received initial reports from the planet which indicate the fighting is fierce between the Draconis Combine defenders and the Suns invaders.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Halstead Station</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Open rebellion in the Free Worlds League</headline><!-- Source: Historical: Brush Wars -->
		<date>3014-06</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Filed 23 May 3014</p><p>Today, we received shocking news, out of New Delos. On May 22, Anton Marik, brother to Captain-General Janos Marik and defender of the Free World League's border with the Capellan Confederation, named himself Captain-General and called for the 'loyal sons and daughters of the League' to support him in overthrowing his brother. Pointing out his brother's recent military failures and self-imposed seclusion, Anton Marik maintained that his brother is unfit to rule and must be replaced for the safety of the realm.</p><p>Sources indicate that while most of the Protectorate and several minor provinces have thrown in their support with Anton Marik while the Duchy of Graham-Marik and the Duchy of Oriente have publicily declared for Captain-General Janos Marik, most provinces in the Free Worlds League have so far either not made any public declaration or have already come forward and invoked the Home Defense Act while declaring their neutrality in any potential conflicts between the brothers.</p><p>We will have more as this story develops. Next, our analysts will discuss what Anton Marik's rebellion will mean for citizens across the League. Stay tuned.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>GB</service>
		<location>Atreus</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Wolf's Dragoons in the League</headline><!-- Source: Wolf's Dragoon Sourcebook -->
		<date>3014-06-02</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>In surprising news, the Wolf's Dragoons have been spotted fighting along-side Anton Marik's rebel forces in the Free Worlds League civil-war. Until the Dragoons joined the fighting, they were believed to still be contracted to the Capellan Confederation performing garrison duty on Carver V. We are unaware at this time if Chancelor Liao has loaned the Dragoons to Anton Marik or if they simply broke contract. One thing is sure, Wolf's Dragoons may be Anton Marik's strongest allies in his bid to dispose the Captain-General.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>New Delos</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Death to traitors</headline>
		<date>3014-06-14</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Today, the Captain-General has returned from his long absence to respond to the threat of his brother Anton Marik. In a lengthy speech to Parliment, the Captain-General showed an energy and determination that has been missing in his few public appearances in recent years.</p><p>During the speech, Captain-General Janos Marik called for, "death to all traitors to the League", and promised that all of his brother's top supporters would be brought to justice, stripped of their tiles and lands and executed as traitors.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>GB</service>
		<location>Atreus</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Provinces declare neutrality</headline>
		<date>3014-07-10</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>In response to Anton Marik's call for revolt against his brother Captain-General Janos Marik, and the Captain-General's call for death to all traitors, the majority of provinces of the Free Worlds League have been quick to declare neutrality and their intentions to stay out of all fighting in order to defend their holdings from the Confederation and Commonwealth.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>GB</service>
		<location>Atreus</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Lyran Commonwealth raids Free Worlds League</headline>
		<date>3014-10-14</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Today, Lyran High Command confirmed reports that the Lyran Commonwealth Armed Forces have begun conducting retalitory raids into the Free Worlds League, in response to the attacks launched on planets across the Commonwealth, including Coventry and Hesperus II over the last decade. While the targets of the raids remain unknown, reports indicate that Commonwealth forces are hitting multiple worlds while the League is distracted by a civil war.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>TBC</service>
		<location>Tharkad</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Sirius and Regulus declare support for Janos Marik</headline>
		<date>3014-11-28</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>After months of refusing to support the Captain-General in his war with his rebel brother, Anton, both Sirius and Regulus have, in exchange for substantial financial subsidies and trade rights, agreed to enter the war on behalf of Captain-General Janos Marik. This comes as a crippling blow to rebel Anton Marik, as he has faced several military setbacks in recent weeks and the addition of fresh troops supporting the Captain-General sounds almost certain defeat for Anton.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>RR</service>
		<location>Regulus</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Marik Civil War updates</headline>
		<date>3014-12-03</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The Civil War between brothers continues to rage in the Free Worlds League. Insider reports indicate that forces loyal to Anton Marik, the rebelling brother to Captain-General Janos Marik, have secured some key victories in their fight to overthrow the leader of the League, including the capture of the 'Mech factories on Irian and Emris IV, as well as additional military manufacturing on Bernardo and Asuncion. However, Anton's forces have suffered several setbacks and reversals that could put an end to this war soon. So far the biggest setbacks have been political and not on the battlefield. While many regions of the Free Worlds League have declared their neutrality in the conflict and have reserved their forces for the defense of their holdings from Liao and Steiner, the Captain-General has secured support of both Sirius and Regulus, two of the most powerful regions of the League. With the new forces they can provide to the Captain-General, even the elite Wolf's Dragoons may not be enough to keep Anton's Rebellion alive.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>New Home</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Light BattleMech gets additional firepower</headline><!-- Source: MUL Online -->
		<date>3015</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Engineers at Coventry Metal works recently finished testing a new variant of the venerable <em>Commando</em> BattleMech. Taking a lession from field reports and history, the hard-hitting short range firepower was modified to incorporate a single large laser. This harkens back to the original model introduced in 2463 and has shown promise in keeping the lightly armored scout in the field longer by reducing the need for resupply and keeping it further from combat.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>DBC</service>
		<location>Coventry</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Anton Marik colludes with Confederation</headline>
		<date>3015-01-23</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Rumors abound that Anton Marik, rebel brother of Captain-General Janos Marik, has been colluding and working closely with the Capellan Confederation before and during his ongoing revolt. While no hard evidence exists, rumors continue to surface, and the fact that the Wolf's Dragoons left the service of Liao early and without any complaints of contract breaking, suggest that the contract was instead passed to Anton Marik by agreement. How can a man that claims to be fighting for the benefit of the Free Worlds League collude with our enemy?</p>]]></desc>
		<service>GB</service>
		<location>Atreus</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Anton Marik killed</headline>
		<date>3015-04-04</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The Civil War between Captain Janos Marik and his brother Anton has ended today. Reports are still coming in from New Delos, however, all reports indicate that some major disagreement between Colonel Jamie Wolf and Anton Marik resulted in the deaths of more than two-dozen Dragoons dependents. After which, Colonel Wolf unleashed the full fury of the Dragoons against Anton Marik and his forces on New Delos.</p><p>Reports indicate that Anton Marik's palatial fortress and headquarters at Cienfuegos was completely leveled by the enrgaged Dragoons and the “Ducal Guards” and the 18th Marik Militia defending him were reportedly hunted down and destroyed to the last man.</p><p>With their leader lost, the already flagging rebel forces are quickly falling to loyalist forces and for the first time in months, the Free Worlds League may be nearing peace.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>GB</service>
		<location>Atreus</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Wolf's Dragoons new employer</headline>
		<date>3015-05-10</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>In an odd twist of fate, after months of bitter fighting for his brother, Wolf's Dragoons have signed a contract with Captain-General Janos Marik's Free Worlds League. While we do not have word on where they will be deployed, it is likely safe to assume the Captain-General will be deploying them against the Lyran Commonwealth in retribution for attacks against the League while the nation was embroiled in a Civil War. Reports indicate that Captain-General Janos Marik personally reached out to the Dragoons to request their services.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Galatea</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Kell Hounds disband</headline>
		<date>3015-07-13</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The Kell Hounds are known throughout the Lyran Commonwealth as an elite mercenary regiment, led by the legendary brothers Morgan and Patrick Kell. However, today that has changed. Reports indicate that nearly two-thirds of the Hounds have disbanded and are seeking work with other commands, apparently at the request of Colonel Morgan Kell, who has himself gone into exile. There is no explanation from the Hounds and Colonel Patrick Kell declined to comment when TBC asked what caused the collapse of the Kell Hounds.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>TBC</service>
		<location>Tharkad</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>New Delos Treason Trials end</headline>
		<date>3015-10-20</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The so-called “New Delos Treason Trials” have finally ended, closing the curtain on a dark period in the long history of the Free Worlds League. The trials were ruthless for those that supported the rebel Anton Marik and fought against Captain-General Janos Marik. The majority of Anton's top supporters and senior officials were found guilty and executed, while lesser supporters were exiled to prison planets or sent to hard labor for their treason. Even the nobles of the League were not spared, even the Captain-General Janos Marik's second son, Gerald Marik, was executed for his part in Anton's Revolt.</p><p>Beyond the bloody results of the treason trials, the Free Worlds League remains a nation divided. The rebels are gone but distrust remains between loyalists and those that remained neutral after invoking the Home Defense Act and the FWL Parliament remains splits politically, with many members at odds with each other or the Captain-General.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>New Home</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Unprecidented look at ComStar intelligence published in new book</headline><!-- Source: ComStar -->
		<date>3020-09</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Our own Jerrold Lewis has been authorized to reveal some of the defining moments of the history of the Blessed Order. <em>ROM: The Blake Years</em> is now available and contains previously classified mission information and descriptions of several key points in history from the eyes of ComStar. Blessed is the Word of Blake.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Terra</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>New Wessex suffers collateral damage during Lyran raid</headline>
		<date>3020-09-20</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>New Wessex is the latest casualty of the war between the Draconis Combine and the Lyran Commonwealth. During an orbital battle earlier this year the LCS <em>St. Brendan</em> entered the atmosphere and suffered a catastrophic engine containment failure. The resulting explosion rained tons of radioactive debris across Jaricosa. Reports are still coming in and medical professionals and scientists are preparing for an increase in cancer and other radiation exposure symptoms of incalcuable levels.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>New Wessex</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Truth Massacre</headline><!-- Source: House Liao (The Capellan Confederation) -->
		<date>3020-09-22</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Capellan Confederation media reports that mercenaries have attacked Truth and butchered the population. Initial estimates indicate that as many as 50,000 people were killed, some dragged from their homes and executed, others fired upon by the mercenary BattleMechs as they fled. So far there has been no official response from the Capellan government. ComStar has dennounced the mercenaries and branded them rogue.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Truth</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Archon Asks Inner Sphere for Peace</headline>
		<date>3020-01</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Once more proving the supremacy of the Lyran Commonwealth over the other power-hungry Successor States, Archon Katrina Stiner directed ComStar to deliver a proposal for peace to all the other lords of the Great Houses. While declaring no hesitation in asserting the primacy of the Commonwealth, Archon Katrina notes the centuries of unrelenting warfare and indicated a desire to find a way for all nations to peacefully coexist. She did, however, halt at reasserting the Archon's traditional insistence on inheritance of the old Star League title First Lord.</p><p>While it is far too soon for the other lords to have responded, experts here at TBC do expect any response. The other House Lords and their ancestors have always resisted the rightful and peaceful rule of House Steiner. It seems unlikely that anything short of outright military victory will bring peace.]]></desc>
		<service>TBC</service>
		<location>Tharkad</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Lyran Commonwealth founds new war college</headline><!-- Source: House Steiner (The Lyran Commonwealth) -->
		<date>3020-10-15</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The Lyran Commonwealth welcomes the first class to be enrolled in the War College of Buena on Fort Buena. The grueling schedule includes not only combat skills as well as academic studies but also technical and logistics managment courses. The intent is to produce officers who are knowledgeable in all aspects of warfare. Only time will tell if these students will live up to the high expectations of the LCAF commanders.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>TBC</service>
		<location>Tharkad</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Pirate forces thwarted on Kimball VI</headline><!-- Source: Technical Readout: 3026 (Revised) -->
		<date>3021</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Glory to the Dragon! The garrison forces proved more than a match for pirate forces attemping to take what rightfully belongs to the Dragon. Enemies of the Draconis Combine beware, a sleeping Dragon wakens at the slightest provocation.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>VotD</service>
		<location>Luthien</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Cal-Boeing releases new VTOL</headline><!-- Source: Technical Readout: 3026 (Revised) -->
		<date>3021</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>After several years of producing the <em>Ferret</em> Cal-Boeing has released a new VTOL to limited fan fare. Cost increases and the general effectiveness of existing designs may kill the new model, the <em>Marten</em>, before it can earn its keep.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>FBC</service>
		<location>Belladonna</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Mercenary memoir tops best sellers</headline><!-- Source: The Mercenary's Handbook -->
		<date>3022</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>A former mercenary, Major Charlene Fellows (Ret), has published a memoir of her time as a mercenary. The book has topped the recent best sellers but it is hard to think it will stay long as it has several scathing reviews of some former employers and their policies. While <em>Under Four Flags: My Life as a Mercenary</em> talks about the trials unique to outfits that work for several employers. Several outlets on Galatea have been scheduling signings and soliciting for more mercenaries to provide their own experiences to capitalize on the interest in the new book. New Avalon Press is reportedly seeking the rights for a movie but would not confirm this rumor.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>FNS</service>
		<location>Galatea</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>BattleMech defeated by lone hovertank in test runs</headline><!-- Source: Technical Readout: 3026 (Revised) -->
		<date>3025</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>S.L. Lewis Incorporated has recently released test footage of their new product dubbed the <em>Savannah Master</em>. This footage shows a lone sample of the hovertank disabling a light BattleMech. Several prominent MechWarriors have already stated that this is less an indication of efficiency and more a flaw in their choice of test pilot. The <em>Savannah Master</em> is equipped with a single medium laser but has a top speed in excess of 200 kph making it one of the fastest ground vehicles ever manufactured. This speed coupled with the fusion engine and energy weapon ensure that this vehicle can spend several days in the field with only driver fatigue as an issue. Several corporations are reportedly interested in purchasing the new vehicle for quick response security forces.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Carlisle</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Verthandi reporting rebellion, militia commander allegedly replaced</headline><!-- Source: Technical Readout: 3026 (Revised) -->
		<date>3025</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Scattered reports from Verthandi indicate that several communities along the Silvan Basin have been taken over by rebel forces. At this time it appears that a <em>Monitor</em> has been captured by these forces and is being used to harass the militia and DCMS forces that are stationed on planet.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Verthandi</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Old scout gets new variant</headline><!-- Source: Technical Readout: 3039 -->
		<date>3025</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Coventry Metal Works has begun producing a new variant of the venerable <em>Commando</em> light 'Mech. This new loadout incorporates a second 6-pack of short-range missiles and a flamer that replace the arm-mounted 4-pack. While this new loadout has significant offensive capabilities for a 25-ton 'Mech, it also reduced the armor by a ton, making the 'Mech that much more vulnerable.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>TMA</service>
		<location>Coventry</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Cyclops, Inc fields new hovertank</headline><!-- Source: MUL online -->
		<date>3025</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The <em>Drillson</em> hovertank is the newest line of vehicles being fielded by the LCAF. Produced by Cyclops, Inc, the <em>Drillson</em> has an impressive arsenal for a hovertank including a large laser, an LRM rack and two SRM racks. This new vehicle will prove to be extremely deadly on open terrain as it has a top speed near 150 kph. Several production runs have already been designated to replace aging machines in the LCAF.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>FNS</service>
		<location>New Earth</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>New BattleMech astonishes crowd in CCAF parade</headline><!-- Source: MUL online -->
		<date>3025</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The Capellan Confederation military once again proves its superiority over the other Successor States with the development of an entirely new BattleMech. The <em>Cataphract</em> will crush the enemies of the Chancellor and help in returning the seat of the Star League to its destined owner. The people of the Confederation will reclaim what is rightfully theirs.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CBS</service>
		<location>Grand Base</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Battlemaster variant defines new role</headline><!-- Source: Technical Readout: 3039 -->
		<date>3025</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>A new variant of the <em>Battlemaster</em> has been showcased to mixed reviews. Replacing 80% of the priomary weapons for various missile systems, the new configuration is more reliant of supplies than many dedicated assault 'Mechs currently fielded. While this does allow commanders to direct a battle from longer ranges, critics are still unsure how it will fare on the battlefield.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>FNS</service>
		<location>Pandora</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Hans Moder retains championship title</headline><!-- Source: Solaris VII Box Set -->
		<date>3025-06</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Filed 22 May 3025</p><p>The Grand Tournament has come to an end for 3025 with Hans Moder winning his second championship in a row. Several of the matches this year were almost too close to call and a number of MechWarriors and fans were injured. Several calls for more saftey measures have been made not only by the stable owners looking to protect their investments but also by the controllers of the games themselves. This has been the most dangerous year yet with failures in two arenas allowing spectator injuries.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>SBC</service>
		<location>Solaris VII</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>ComStar Publishing releases new technical readout files</headline><!-- Source: Technical Readout: 3025 Revised -->
		<date>3025-07</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Filed 05 June 3025</p><p>ComStar Publishing has released a new technical readout showcasing many of the more common BattleMech designs. While this is no way complete, the Order hopes that readers will find these data collections useful in the field. Blessed is the Word of Blake.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Terra</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>New champion crowned during Solaris Games</headline><!-- Source: Solaris VII Player's Handbook --><!-- No canon date -->
		<date>3026-05-24</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Two-time Solaris champion, Hans Moder has been defeated by Philip Capet, a former MechWarrior in the AFFS. The new champion has been fighting as a Davion independent for the last several years in an ancient <em>Rifleman</em> that he says was given to him by Hanse Davion himself. The former champion is recovering from his injuries and was unavailable for comment at this time.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>SBC</service>
		<location>Solaris VII</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>AFFS Announced Operation Galahad</headline>
		<date>3026-08-10</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The Armed Forces of the Federated Suns announced Operation Galahad today. These wargames will be some of the largest ever conducted, involving ten regiments of AFFS BattleMechs and more than 100 infantry and armor regiments.</p><p>According the AFFS spokespersons, Galahad is "intended to increase our vigilance by rehearsing defensive troop movements so that if one of our enemies dares attack us, we can make a devastating retaliation."</p><p>Pundits have called the exercises expensive, disruptive and controversial, but as ever, House Davion's military follows the orders of the First Prince.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>FSNS</service>
		<location>New Avalon</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>AFFS announces massive wargames</headline><!-- Source: NAIS The Fourth Succession War Military Atlas Volume 1 -->
		<date>3026-09</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Filed 3025-08-10</p><p>The military announced today that an undesclosed number of troops would be involved in a set of wargame exercises dubbed Operation GALAHAD. The operation is set to begin sometime next month and will involve large numbers of troops in both the Draconis and Capellan Marches. While the AFFS maintains that these exercises are only to maintain force readiness, several worlds that host the large numbers of troops worry that these types of undertakings will change the economic atmosphere of those worlds. Increases in demand for staple items hanve already been reported as products are purchased in bulk ahead of the anticipated wargame. Locals are encouraged to voice their concerns with their governmental representatives to ensure that hoarding and price gouging are reported and any issues with AFFC personnel are documented.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>FNS</service>
		<location>New Avalon</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Grand Tournament begins, Capet looks to keep title</headline><!-- No canon date -->
		<date>3027-01</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Philip Capet, the 3026 Grand Champion, has stated that he plans to retain his title this year. While there have been a few close calls, sources close to the Champion tell us that several challengers have already attempted to remove him from the tournament outside of the arenas. Capet has refused to answer any questions on his plans for the upcoming battles, only that he is confident in his abilities as a MechWarrior and his technical team.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>SBC</service>
		<location>Solaris VII</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>AFFS Announced Operation Galahad '27</headline>
		<date>3027-01</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The Armed Forces of the Federated Suns announced a repetition of last year's Operation Galahad, named Galahad 3027. These wargames will be some even larger than last year's, involving 30 regiments of AFFS BattleMechs and more than 200 infantry and armor regiments.</p><p>In order to make these massive troop movements, the Davion government announced sweeping plans to briefly nationalize a number of the nation's merchant marine hulls. The exact numbers of JumpShips and DropShips requisitioned was not released, but sources say the number is "substantial."</p><p>Pundits have repeated calls that the exercises are expensive, disruptive, and have condemned the unquestionably effect this will have on the Suns' domestic economy.</p><p>Our Lyran bureaus are reporting that the LCAF is running a similar exercise in Steiner space, called Operation Thor.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>FSNS</service>
		<location>New Avalon</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Galahad and Thor Run Without ComStar?</headline>
		<date>3027-02</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>MercNet has heard an incredible rumor about the upcoming Steiner and Davion war games that seems too incredible to be true. If it <strong>IS</strong> true, it seems like the height of Davion hubris.</p><p>According to rumor, neither military is using ComStar HPGs to coordinate their movements.</p><p>Every nation, every mercenary unit, just plain <em>everyone</em> uses ComStar. It's how things get done. But if the Steiners and the Davions think they can do better while throwing dozens of regiments around, I guess more power to them?</p><p>Here at MercNet, shooters, we still recommend you use your friendly neighborhood HPG to keep in touch.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>MercNet</service>
		<location>Galatea</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>AFFS officer tried for treason: Exiled by First Prince</headline><!-- Source: Warrior: EnGarde -->
		<date>3027-02-10</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Late last month the ongoing trial of Major Justin Allard came to an explosive conclusion with a personal appearance by First Prince Hanse Davion. The disruption ended with the dismissal and exile of the Major, stripping of title and family name. Justin Xiang was on trial for treason against the Federated Suns for actions taken while in command of a training battalion on Kittery and collusion with known Capellan Confederation personnel. Sources close to the trial indicated that several high ranking officers within the AFFS were witnesses or provided testimony during this trial.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>New Avalon</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Solaris VII Grand Tournament upsets</headline><!-- Source: Warrior: EnGarde -->
		<date>3027-04</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Filed 20 March 3027</p><p>A newcomer has arrived on the Game World that has fans and owners alike seeing red. Justin Xiang, formerly of the AFFS, has defeated a loyal Davion MechWarrior and issued a challenge that anyone who supports the First Prince will die at his hands. Recently exiled from the realm, Xiang has already killed Peter Armstrong in a duel. This has many game watchers wondering if this MechWarrior is more bark than bite, or if her really has what it takes to go to the top.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>SBC</service>
		<location>Solaris VII</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Xiang Kills Davion MechWarrior, challenges champion</headline><!-- Source: Warrior: EnGarde -->
		<date>3027-04-27</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Another victim has fallen to Justin Xiang, Billy Wolfson of Lord Brighton's Stable was killed in the arena following an unorthadox attack by Xiang's heavily modified <em>Centurion</em>. After the match, Xiang challenged the current champion, Philip Capet, to fight him in the arena and that he is only delaying his death. Former champion, Gray Noton declined to speak to our sources regarding his apparent teaming with Xiang. Xiang, currently low in the rankings, is not yeat in a position to issue a formal challenge and there is no word on a response from Capet at this time.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>SBC</service>
		<location>Solaris VII</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>New Champion named: Davion supporters shocked, bodies turn up</headline><!-- Source: Warrior: EnGarde -->
		<date>3027-05-30</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Philip Capet was killed in what game watchers have called one of the hottest feuds that Solaris VII has ever seen. Fighting in the name of the Capellan Confederation, Justin Xiang executed Capet during a match in the Ishiyama arena, disabling Capet's 'Mech and then deliberately shooting the cockpit. Davion supporters were shocked by this act of barbarism and many of the Stable owners are said to have voiced displeasure that he could be named champion with such an action. Rumors have been heard that this fight, one that both MechWarriors agreed to, was rigged and that Xiang would not trust Capet to keep the secret as several people close to Xiang have recently disappeared or have turned up dead, including former champion Gray Noton with whom he was seen several times since his arrival.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>SBC</service>
		<location>Solaris VII</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Davion-Steiner wedding in the works, First Prince announces plans</headline><!-- Source: TBD-->
		<date>3027-10-30</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Earlier this month, First Prince Hanse Davion announced that he is betrothed to Archon-Designate Melissa Steiner. The wedding date has not yet been announced but this remarkable event stands to shape the Inner Sphere for generations to come. Uniting the two most powerful realms will create an opportunity for peace and prosperity to spread and improve the lives of the people of both the Federated Suns and the Lyran Commonwealth. We encourage all peoples of the Federated Suns to keep a watchful eye on the FNS press releases to ensure you are staying up to date on the latest news.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>FNS</service>
		<location>New Avalon</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Archon-Designate to wed First Prince</headline><!-- Source: TBD-->
		<date>3027-10-31</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>In an unprecidented move, the leaders of the Lyran Commonwalth have chosen to allow a wedding of Archon-Designate Melissa Steiner to First Prince Hanse Davion. While bringing the two realms closer together will provide opportunities for peace, the lack of a large border will challenge even the most accomplished military commanders to provide for mutual support. This could also serve to galvanize the other realms to unite their forces against the union of the Steiner and Davion.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>TBC</service>
		<location>Tharkad</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>TharHes Industries reveals new light BattleMech</headline><!-- Source: MUL Online -->
		<date>3028-02-21</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The Public Information Office at TharHes Industries on Tharkad has issued a press release with details of their newest light BattleMech model. Designated the <em>Wolfhound</em>, it is designed to operate for long periods away from supply lines. While much of the information regarding the new chassis is still classified, the spokesperson stated that the simulations have proven the capabilities of the machine. The LCAF will be receiving the majority of the first runs and combat trials are expected to begin on several planets.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>TBC</service>
		<location>Tharkad</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Amazons in the Periphery?</headline><!-- Source: TBD -->
		<date>3028-04-04</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Earlier this year several reports from the Periphery indicated that a fracture was forming in one of the largest bandit kingdoms. New reports from the Explorer Corps seem to indicate that a new group has taken several planets from the Oberon Confederation. This new group claims to be named the Greater Valkyrate and seems to be based on the ideal of female superiority. Several male captives report torture and mutilation while most female prisoners state they were treated well. So far there has been no indication of hostility towards the Successor States but ComStar is warning all JumpShip captains to be extra cautious when traveling near their claimed borders.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Terra</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Gray Death Legion commits war crimes</headline><!-- Source: The Price of Glory -->
		<date>3028-04-24</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>ComStar has issued a declaration stating that the mercenary unit, the Gray Death Legion, commanded by Grayson Carlyle is now listed as Wanted and all remaining assets not with the unit have been frozen or siezed. Reports indicate that a lance of Legion BattleMechs destroyed a biosphere habitat on Sirius V causing the death of over 12-million civilians. Officials from the Free Worlds League has called for a formal inquiry of the unit as well as an immediate annulment of their contract. Bounties are expected to be issued in the next few weeks on Grayson Carlyle and his forces.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Sirius V</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>"Here, My Love..." says Hanse Davion to Melissa Steiner</headline>
		<date>3028-08-21</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>No one thought, before the fact, that the wedding of First Prince Hanse Davion of the Federated Suns to Melissa Steiner, daughter of Archon Katrina Steiner of the Lyran Commonwealth, would be a boring affair, but no one could have anticipated this.</p><p>The wedding itself was beautiful, everyone agreed. And the reception after had collected more Successor State lords than any even since the fall of the Star League so many centuries ago. But when it came time for the toasts...</p><p>The bride went first, gifting her husband a regiment of 'Mechs. Kind of tacky, some might have said. But in line. What else could a Davion prince want more?</p><p>The entire Inner Sphere found out when Hanse Davion rose to toast his wife. "I give you the Capellan Confederation!" Davion proclaimed.</p><p>People went <em>crazy</em>. Most of us in the press thought that was it, but later in the hotel lobbies and bars we heard the first reports from ComStar: Davion regiments had crossed into the Confederation in overwhelming strength.</p><p>Hanse Davion clearly means to deliver on his promise. Which means, fellow mercenaries, business is about to get <em>good</em>.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>MercNet</service>
		<location>Terra</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Highlanders return to Northwind</headline><!-- Source: Handbook: House Davion -->
		<date>3029-02</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The mercenary unit, the Northwind Highlanders have returned to Northwind under Davion banners. The apparent breach of contract from the Capellan Confederation comes on the heels of several regions near Terra seeing heavy fighting between the Draconis Combine and the Federated Suns. While reports of illness have hospitals overloaded, casualties from the recent fighting have prevented many from seeking treatment. It will be interesting to see what arrangements were made with the former Capellan mercenaries and how the First Prince will treat them in the future.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>FNS</service>
		<location>Northwind</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Official ComStar Release: PRIORITY MESSAGE FOLLOWS</headline><!-- Source: The Warrior Trilogy -->
		<date>3029-06-01</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>By order of the Primus: The Federated Suns are hereby interdicted. Any attempts to violate this will be treated as criminal actions and handled appropriately with ComStar oversight.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Terra</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Federated troops unleash chemical weapons</headline><!-- Source: TBD -->
		<date>3029-11</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Federated Commonwealth troops willingly reployed chemical weapons on the civilians and defenders of Wei in their attempt to claim the planet. While casualties were high, the planetary government was able to escape the planet, leaving the tainted wasteland to the treacherous FedCom commanders. The lives of those lost will be avenged by his Celestial Wisdom.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CBS</service>
		<location>Sian</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Official ComStar Release: PRIORITY MESSAGE FOLLOWS</headline><!-- Source: The Warrior Trilogy -->
		<date>3029-12-07</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>By order of the Primus: The Federated Suns interdiction is lifted.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Terra</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>New member of the Royal Family!</headline>
		<date>3030-05-01</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The Federated Commonwealth has a new member of the royal family. On 12 April 3030 Archon-Designate Melissa Steiner-Davion and First Prince Hanse Davion welcomed Victor Steiner-Davion to the world. The new Prince has a long road ahead of him to see the continuation of the Federated Commonwealth into the next generation. All of us here at the TBC wish the Prince a long and joyous life and congratulate the the royal family on its new member.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>TBC</service>
		<location>Tharkad</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Grave Walkers mercenary unit announce long-term contract with BioHarvest, Inc</headline><!-- Source: Touring the Stars: Bone-Norman -->
		<date>3031</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The MRB and the Grave Walkers have announced that one of the regiments for the mercenary unit is on a long-term hire with BioHarvest, Inc. This announcement comes on the tail of a press conference by BioHarvest executives revealing that several new species of plants discoverd on Bone-Norman have incredibly potent medicinal properties. The contract details have not been announced but many analysts assume that this move is a way for BioHarvest, Inc to protect their discoveries and discourage any other competition from trying to stake their claims.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>DBC</service>
		<location>Bone-Norman</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Dragoons bloody but not broken says CO</headline><!-- Source: Mercenary's Handbook 3055 -->
		<date>3031-10</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Filed 06 September 3031</p><p>In a statement made today to assembled press Colonel Jamie Wolf addressed claims that the mercenary unit would disband. Several analysts predicted that recent losses to the DCMS and increasing debts would force the unit to begin liquidating its assets. While this may have been more hopeful thinking than actual data, the Colonel assured potential employers, "It may take time, but we'll be back."</p>]]></desc>
		<service>MercNet</service>
		<location>Galatea</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Dragoons field new battalion, missions already under way</headline><!-- Source: Mercenary's Handbook 3055 -->
		<date>3032-01</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Filed 16 December 3031</p><p>Wolf's Dragoons has announced the formation of a new force in a rather unconventional way. Holovids of the unit in action on Tsinghai are leaving many wondering where the new force was hiding. Some media representatives are even calling into question the validity of the footage as there was no indication of the battalion prior to the footage being released by the Dragoons. So for the MRB has refused to comment as all contract specifics are tightly controlled. Colonel Wolf has stated that the new force is commanded by Colonel Natasha Kerensky, a notable MechWarrior with decades of combat experience.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>MercNet</service>
		<location>Galatea</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>A new Successor State is born</headline><!-- Source: Historical: War of 3039 -->
		<date>3034-04</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Filed 13 March 3034</p><p>Gunji-no-Kanrei Theodore Kurita formally acknowledged the creation of the Free Rasalhague Republic earlier this year. The proclaimed Prince of the Free Rasalhague Republic, Haakon Magnusson has now created a realm for himself from both Draconis Combine as well as Federated Commonwealth worlds in the former Rasalhague Military District. Only time will tell how this new power will be treated in the large political world that is the Inner Sphere. Good luck Prince Magnusson, you are going to need it.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Rasalhague</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Dragon gifts life to realm</headline><!-- Source: Historical: War of 3039 -->
		<date>3034-03-20</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Priority Broadcast Filed 13 March 3034</p><p>Glory to the Dragon! By the will of Gunji-no-Kanrei Theodore Kurita, the Free Rasalhague Republic has been given independence from the Draconis Combine. All DCMS forces have been ordered to turn over their facilities to representatives of the FRR government.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>VotD</service>
		<location>Rasalhague</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Free World League declares war on Andurien</headline><!-- Source: Historical: Brush Wars -->
		<date>3035-07</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Priority Broadcast Filed 27 June 3035</p><p>In a statement today by Captain-General Duncan Marik, the bomb that killed Captain-General Thomas Marik and several other members of the senior FWLM staff has been determined to have been manufactured and planted by operatives of the Ductchy of Andurien. The Captain-General announced that anyone with ties to those responsible for the terrorist action will be found and that the Dutchy is guilty of the highest treason and will be treated as criminals with all opportunities for diplomacy off the table.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Atreus</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Marik familiy announces death of Captain-General</headline><!-- Source: Historical: Brush Wars -->
		<date>3037-03</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Filed 09 February 3037</p><p>Representatives of the Andurien government recently released the body of Duncan Marik to a liason of the FWLM after he was killed on Xanthe III. The announcement of his death has spawned mixed reactions from many worlds. His ascention to the position of Captain-General came after many of the Marik family were killed in June of 3035. Thomas Marik is expected to make several statements to the nation in the coming days.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Atreus</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Outworlds Alliance welcomes new member</headline><!-- Source: The Periphery, 2nd Edition -->
		<date>3038</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Announcements from the Outworlds Alliance indicate that the President and family have welcomed a daughter, Patrice Avellar.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>TBC</service>
		<location>Alpheratz</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>"Toothpuller" sighted with Sorenson's Sabres</headline><!-- Source: Sword and Dragon -->
		<date>3038</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The personal BattleMech of Melinda Carlyle, "Toothpuller" is rumored to now be in the hands of Sorenson's Sabres. Carlyle was featured as a notable <em>Panther</em> pilot in the ComStar published Technical Readout: 3025. Witnesses claim the BattleMech was severely damaged and that it appeared the cockpit was destroyed. No word from Hansen's Roughriders has announced the death of Carlyle and at this time the DCMS has refused to comment on any actions on Delacruz.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>MercNet</service>
		<location>Galatea</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Heir to Taurian Concordant falls ill during tour of realm</headline><!-- Source: The Periphery, 2nd Edition -->
		<date>3038</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>News from the Periphery indicated that Janice Calderon, heir to Thomas Calderon and the Taurian Concordant has fallen ill during a recent tour of Brisbane. The planet is known for virulent strains of disease that are nearly always fatal and resist treatments of even many Successor State facilities. Details are unavailable as to the specifics of the illness but those of us here at the DBC with Ms. Calderon a speedy recovery.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>DBC</service>
		<location>Taurus</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Imstar Aerospace unveils new fighter variant</headline><!-- Source: Objectives: Federated Suns -->
		<date>3038</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The <em>Defender II</em>, a new modification of the <em>Defender</em> fighter, has been unveiled to buyers across the Free Worlds League. This new fighter comes equipped with advanced fire control equipment that improve the effectiveness of its long range missiles. The company has already taken several orders from militia forces and corporate officers are anticipating increasing demand as the new craft is tested.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>INI</service>
		<location>Amity</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Unrest on Galtor III</headline><!-- Source: NAIS The Fourth Succession War Military Atlas Volume 1 -->
		<date>3039-03</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Several recent protests on Galtor III have caused local militia units several problems and are continuing to spread through several cities. The recent arrival of Kurita forces has reportedly created several situations of abuse at the hands of security forces. While this is not unheard of with planets who recently face an invading force, most uprisings are quelled quickly by the occupying force as a return to normalcy is more economically beneficial. This is not the first time that DCMS forces have taken the planet and some historians are looking at the First Succession War as a template for how things will be moving forward.</p><p>The question that is on everyone's mind is how will the First Prince assure the people of Galtor that he can in-fact protect them from the predations of the Draconis Combine when they have already taken the planet as their own?</p>]]></desc>
		<service>FNS</service>
		<location>New Avalon</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Archon abdicates, names Melissa Steiner-Davion as replacement</headline><!-- Source: Historical: War of 3039 -->
		<date>3039-04</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Priority Broadcast Filed 15 March 3039</p><p>A new era of leadership has now come to the Federated Commonwealth with the abdication of Archon Katrina Steiner, taking the title of Archon-Emeritus. Her daughter, and wife of First Prince Hanse Davion, Archon Melissa Steiner-Davion has been announced as her successor. We at the DBC hope that our new Archon has many years of peace ahead of her and that she will not forget the people of the Lyran Commonwealth.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>DBC</service>
		<location>Donegal</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Federated Commonwealth celebrates birth of child</headline><!-- Source: 20 Year Update -->
		<date>3039-04</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Priority Broadcast Filed 15 March 3039</p><p>A new child of First Prince Hanse Davion and Archon Melissa Steiner has been announced. Yvonne Steiner-Davion was born to the first family on March 15th on Liao during a tour of the Sarna March. Details regarding the pregnancy were scarce but all reports seem to indicate the child and mother are in good health and will be returning to Tharkad for official ceremonies later this month. We wish the royal family health and wellness from all of us at the TBC.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>TBC</service>
		<location>Liao</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>First Prince to Coordinator, "We have waited long enough for justice!"</headline><!-- Source: Historical: War of 3039 -->
		<date>3039-04-20</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Priority Broadcast Filed 15 April 3039</p><p>First Prince Hanse Davion announced today that the Federated Commonwealth will no longer sit by while its citizens are brutalized by Kuritan thugs. In response to several incidents of former Federated worlds being dealth with harshly by armed Kuritan officials and military personnel the First Prince declared a war of liberation on those worlds. During his speech this morning from New Avalon he announced that "Steps must be taken to deal with the Kuritan tyranny." Officials who spoke with the TBC on the condition of anonymity this afternoon indicated that several elite units are mobilizing and will be ready to attack the Draconis Combine as early as the next few weeks.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>TBC</service>
		<location>Tharkad</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Theft of vehicle reveals local patriots</headline><!-- Source: Historical: War of 3039 -->
		<date>3039-05</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Filed 04 April 3039</p><p>An incident earlier this week has shown that there is honor among thieves. An officer in the AFFS whos personal vehicle was stolen just happened to contain classified information which was left intact with a note after the vehicle was recovered. While the thief is still unknown, the note read that he or she was,"still a patriot." At this time, there is no word on the repercussions of this event on for the officer in question, nor has the AFFS made any statements on the contents of the material.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>RR</service>
		<location>Robinson</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Fifth Succession War?</headline><!-- Source: Historical: War of 3039 -->
		<date>3039-06</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Reports of attacks against the Combine worlds of Alrakis, Alnasi, Kessel, Vega, Altais, and Konstance have been filtering through official and unoffical channels. This follows a declaration of liberation by First Prince Hanse Davion last month. These events have stunned many who predicted that the Steiner-Davion marriage was going to usher in a new era of peace after the attempts to conquer the Capellan Confederation. Analysts are struggling to piece these new reorts together and anticipate the DCMS response.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Outreach</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Solaris tension rises as war approaches</headline><!-- Source: TBD -->
		<date>3039-05-07</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Authorities have reported increasing numbers of incidents involving Draconis and Federated citizens and stable affiliated MechWarriors as things heat up throughtout the Inner Sphere. Several MechWarriors have been arrested and at least four civilian deaths have been reported. Stable owners have been warned that any incident will be met with harsh punishment and that any MechWarriors identified inciting violence outside of the arena will be treated accordingly. As a result of the increasing tension on the Commonwealth/Combine border, arena attendance has been higher than normal and betting has seen a large increase in volume. Officials went on record to say "No matter the situation out there on those worlds, Solaris will always be a place where people can come and get away from all of the politics, and maybe make a profit from it in the process."</p>]]></desc>
		<service>SBC</service>
		<location>Solaris VII</location>
	</newsItem>
		<newsItem>
		<headline>Riding A Pale Horse</headline>
		<date>3039-05-11</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The Gray Death Legion achieved fame with its exploits on Helm and its subsequent accomplishments in the Fourth Succession War. The War of 3039 has seen this elite mercenary unit in action once more. Our correspondent, Nathalie Myers, accompanied them to Altais and brings this report.<br>Myers: I’m here on the outskirts of New Ross with Legion officer Davis McCall. Major McCall, can you tell me what happened here?<br>McCall: It were a reet mess, lassie. It all gaed ta bugry when t’ beacon fritzed and me and the lads and lasses were chucked all o’er the toon. We wuz skittering all o’er the toon like Caledonian flitter.<br>Myers: So it was a confused landing?<br>McCall: Aye, more chappit tatties than rummledethump. Wee Andy’s haed his heed knocked off in’t first seconds but ah winnae let summet like dat gae me doon and wasnae disjaskit. Ah cracked the Sassenach that battered wee Andy and gae him a kickin’ before gannin’ back tae the sodger lads, rallyin’ them for a counterattack.<br>Myers: You weren’t going to stay on the defensive?<br>McCall: Ahm nae bampot, lassie. I ken the need tae kick ‘em Snakes in t’ bollocks—pardon my French—while they’re nae ready. Those bogles were gae’n themsels organized so yis had tae act.<br>Myers: Did it work?<br>McCall: Well, lassie, there ye hae a gid question. Ah dinnae ‘spect ‘em tae bugger off but they’re hard scunners and gae as gid as they got.<br>Myers: What was your thought when you realized that? Were you afraid for your life?<br>McCall: I’d be touched if ah wasnae worried, but I’m nae eejit. We werenae feenisht yet, particular if wis helt till Gray show’d up.<br>Myers: You expected Colonel Carlyle to rescue you?<br>McCall: Nae, lassie, but he hae a knack o’turnin’ up when he’s needed, ye ken?<br>[Colonel Carlyle arrives and whispers briefly to McCall]<br>McCall: Sure Gray, no problem. I’ll be right over once I’m finished here.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>DBC</service>
		<location>Altais</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>The pale horse</headline><!-- Source: Historical: War of 3039 -->
		<date>3039-06</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Filed 11 May 3039</p><p>Nathalie Myers, recently imbedded with the Gray Death Legion, witnessed first hand the high cost of war. In an interview with the command staff, she was told about several attempted ambushes and brutal fighting within the city with no concern for collateral damage. Fighting of this magnitude is typically avoided but in this case the forces involved slugged it out in the streets. Reports from local media indicate several injuries but word has yet to come in on any fatalities.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>DBC</service>
		<location>Altais</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>AFFS battalion commander flees battle, steals JumpShip</headline><!-- Source: Field Manual: Mercenaries, Revised -->
		<date>3039-09</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The defenders of Halstead Station are a little shorthanded lately as reports of an AFFS officer leaving his post along with his entire battalion including DropShips and a JumpShip have been coming through unofficial channels. AFFS leaders have so far declined to comment on this report and have denied any morale issues within their officer corps. Several veteran units were stationed on the planet and it is not known at this time who the officer was or their unit affiliation.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Halstead Station</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Davion commander mutinies, flees Federation space </headline><!-- Source: Field Manual: Mercenaries, Revised -->
		<date>3039-09</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Glory to the Dragon! Davion forces flee from Halstead Station in the face of superior MechWarriors of the Sword of Light regiments taking with them several DropShips as well as a JumpShip. The commander chose to abandon his post without honor when he was informed of the elite regiments arriving on planet. He was said to have addressed his troops from low orbit on his intent to join a Periphery bandit force. This latest incident shows just how much Federated officers fear the Combine military and can clearly see that they stand no chance against the will of the Coordinator.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>VotD</service>
		<location>Halstead Station</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>General Motors slated to revolutionize fire-fighting</headline><!-- Source: MUL Online -->
		<date>3044</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>General Motors has announced the pending release of a new IndustrialMech designed specifically for firefighting. The <em>Pompier</em> was developed with the input of several industry leaders to use the latest technology to assist conventional fire fighting teams with large and dangerous fires. While the release date is not for several weeks, GM public affairs has stated that pre-orders have been better than expected.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Kathil</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline><![CDATA[Rumors stirring of new <em>Phoenix Hawks</em> in Federated Commonwealth]]></headline><!-- Source: MUL Online -->
		<date>3043</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Several sources on contested planets near the Federated Commonwealth border have indicated that a new model of <em>Phoenix Hawk</em> have been sighted. An ancient design, unmistakable BattleMech has rumored to be packing more of a punch than usual while staying out of range of its opponents. The AFFC media liason has not returned any requests for verification of this information so we can only speculate on what this means.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>FBC</service>
		<location>Outreach</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>New aerospace fighter launched</headline><!-- Source: MUL Online -->
		<date>3044</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Glory to the Dragon! The Draconis Combine again proves its mastery over the fraudulent and corrupt Successor States who claim to have a right to the Star League. Death will rain from the heavens in the newest variant of the <em>Slayer</em>, a true marvel of engineering from Wakazashi Enterprises. Technological advancements have made this the most deadly fighter of its class and will defeat many times its weight in BattleMechs.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>VotD</service>
		<location>Dover</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Industry leaders merge in FWL</headline><!-- Source: TBD -->
		<date>3044</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Austen Vale Ordnance and Armstrong Industries recently announced plans to merge the two companies under a single board of directors. The new company, Austen-Armstrong Industries, will combine the experts of both companies who were developing several new long-arms for military applications. Industry critics question whether this merger will create the developments that are being promised. Spokesmen from both companies held a joint press conference early last week and promised that the new products will increase the market value of the company by several margins.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Abadon</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Eridani Light Horse change of command</headline><!-- Source: Twilight of the Clans -->
		<date>3045</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The famed Eridani Light Horse mercenary unit welcomed a new commanding officer earlier this month with the retirement of Brevet General William Peterson. The new commander, Brevet General Ariana Winston has had a distinguished career in the unit and is said to have won over the loyalty of every officer she has worked with. Everyone here at MercNet wish you a long and honorable career General Winston.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>MercNet</service>
		<location>Outreach</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Mercenary turned author, from weapons to words</headline><!-- Source: The Saga of the Gray Death Legion -->
		<date>3045</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The Gray Death Legion mercenary unit has been know throughout the Inner Sphere as an example of what can be done in the face of adversity. Formed from battle and tested against treachery, thy have proven never to bet against them. Now they have thrown their hat into another type of battle, one for sales. Lori Kalmar has released a book detailing her time with the GDL titled <em>'Mechs of Flesh and Blood</em>. While critics have reviewed the book poorly, saying that it looks like it was written as a holodrama straight from the Free worlds League. Combat veteran and reviewer Gregory Barklette, provided one of the best reviews, "While written basically, it captures the intent of battlefield life, with the ups and downs that being in a merc outfit can bring." It is unknown at this time if a second volume will be coming from Avalon Press.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>FNS</service>
		<location>New Avalon</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>New technologies for aging industries</headline><!-- Source: TechManual -->
		<date>3045</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>IndustrialMech manufacturing companies across the Inner Sphere are being upgraded with a recently developed form of myomer. This myomer allows for heavier loads to be transported as it increases the strength of the IndustrialMech exponentially. There are already massive orders for this new equipment and stock prices for companies proven to be suppliers of the myomer have risen significantly. Several Solaris VII stables are reportedly purchasing large quantities of this enhanced myomer, since there are no current events for IndustrialMechs one can only assume that they will be attempting to modify it for BattleMechs.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Outreach</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Venerable command BattleMech gets facelift</headline><!-- Source: MUL Online -->
		<date>3045</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The <em>Cyclops</em>, a common command BattleMech, has been fielded with a new variant, the CP-11-A. Sacrificing some of the short-range power of the Zeus-36 autocannon, the new model is equipped with a Zeus Slingshot Gauss Rifle which has an incredible range of 660 meters. While slightly less powerful, this new weapon system allows a commander or other pilot to engage enemies from ranges that many 'Mechs will struggle to effectively return fire from. This upgrade is also one of many produced locally within the Free Worlds League by Irian BattleMechs Unlimited.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>INI</service>
		<location>Irian</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>War declaration from Taurian Concordant</headline><!-- Source: TBD -->
		<date>3045-07-10</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>This is a Taurian Public Broadcasting breaking news alert! Frederick Gunston on site here at an emergency meeting of the leaders of the TDF and other senior governmental officials. We are anticipating an announcement from the Marshal of the IV Corps here in a mom... Wait, the message is coming through now. "A state of war now exists between the Taurian Concordant and the Federated Commonwealth. A recent attack has left several dozen civilian casualties and their blood is on the hands of the mercenaries and their Davion puppeteers. We will not stand idle as forces kill our people indiscriminately with brutality unseen since the fall of the Star League. Our forces are on full military alert and as of today all Davion forces in Taurian space will be considered hostile if they do not immediately surrender. We will have justice for our fallen. All civilians on worlds near the Commonwealth border are encouraged to practice their..." As we can see this situation has quickly escalated. If you or any of your family members live on those worlds we encourage you to seek out your nearest shelter and assist those who cannot. This has been a Taurian Public Broadcasting breaking news alert.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>TPB</service>
		<location>Taurus</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Fox's Teeth take a bite out of "Big Mac"</headline><!-- Source: Historical: War of 3039 -->
		<date>3045-07-19</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>In response to an attack last year, the forces of McKinnon's Raiders have devastated McCarron's Armored Cavalry on Menke. The attack is said to have damaged several facilities belonging to the MAC and the Capellan government has announced that they will be funding the rebuilding of the unit in response to the Davion aggression. Casualty reports are incomplete but it is reported that at least a company of BattleMechs and several dozen vehicles were destroyed along with Fort McCarron. Forces on both sides of the border are at a heightened state of alert as the fallout from this revenge attack settles into diplomacy.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Menke</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Davion forces attack Pinard!</headline><!-- Source: TBD -->
		<date>3045-08-22</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Davion empolyed mercenaries have raided a supply depot on Pinard owned by Vandenburg Mechanized Industries (VMI). During the raid several civilians were killed as the BattleMech forces assaulted the main complex. An announcement by Protector Calderon has stated that this raid and the recent increase in Davion forces along the border indicated that the Federated Commonwealth has already initiated a state of war between the two nations. Mercenary units along both sides of the border are warned that no official response from Davion media outlets or diplomatic decrees have verified this statement.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Pinard</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Thumper sales plummet, Brooks Incorporated cancels production</headline><!-- Source: Technical Readout: 3075 -->
		<date>3046</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Brooks Incorporated, the main supplier of <em>Thumper</em> artillery pieces in the Inner Sphere announced last month that this would be the last year that the vehicles will be produced ending over three centuries of the model-line. Recent sales have been slowly declining and representatives have been hinting that the assembly line will be retooled to produce other vehicles, ensuring employment for the factory workers on the effected planets.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Andurien</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Hunchback receives facelift</headline><!-- Source: Technical Readout: 3050 Upgrade -->
		<date>3046</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The venerable <em>Hunchback</em> has recieved its first official upgrade with Helm technologies. The design designation HBK-5M has undergone a complete redesign of its cooling system and adds a little more firepower with a Sunglow pulse laser. Kali Yama executives are limiting the production of this BattleMech for the first six-months to units of the FWLM and mercenaries loyal to House Marik. Further information about this new varaint can be found on MercNet or by contacting Kali Yama Weapons Industries Incorporated directly.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Kalidasa</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Free Worlds League christens new JumpShip</headline><!-- Source: Technical Readout: 3057 (Revised) -->
		<date>3046</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Citing a press release from SelaSys Inc., a new JumpShip has been launched ahead of what they hope to be a successful line. The <em>Tramp</em>-class JumpShip is still a prototype but serves as proof that the technologies of the Star League are not that far away.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>INI</service>
		<location>Loyalty</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Grim Determination takes out the trash</headline><!-- Source: Field Manual: Free Worlds League -->
		<date>3046</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Several battle reports have been submitted to public record of an engagement by the mercenary unit Grim Determination on Sarna. Forces of the FWLM attempted to raid the planet and were defeated with the mecenaries reporting an OPFOR loss of over 40%. Well done Colonel Trent and the troops of Grim Determination.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>MercNet</service>
		<location>Sarna</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Ancient factory resumes production</headline><!-- Source: Field Manual: Mercenaries -->
		<date>3046</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The newest company on the block, Norse-Storm Technologies Incorporated, have recently held a ribbon-cutting ceremony at the restored Loxley production facility. As a former mercenary unit the company has been working on rebuilding the facility for some time. Investors are wary that the company may not have the financial or corporate capability to maintain this new facility with technologies rapidly advancing in the BattleMech market.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>FNS</service>
		<location>Loxley</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>FWL passes controversial military reorganization</headline><!-- Source: Field Manual: Free Worlds League -->
		<date>3046-04-11</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The Free Worlds League has passed an act completely reorganizing their military components. This act, dubbed the Military Reorganization Act dissolves all provencial forces and makes them a part of the larger FWLM and forces them to accept new recruits from all sources of raw talent. Several unit commanders have bucked against this act stating that the influx of untested or otherwise undesireable soldiers will have a negative effect on the readiness and discipline of the FWLM. There are reports that many of the commanders have stepped down instead of accepting these new members and at least one has taken loyal forces and fled Marik space.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Atreus</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Recovered technology heralds new Jenners</headline><!-- Source: Technical Readout: 3050 Upgrade -->
		<date>3046</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The <em>Jenner</em> BattleMech is once again in production! After nearly two centuries, recent discoveries have allowed for new <em>Jenners</em> to be produced by Luthien Armor Works. Long associated with the Draconis Combine this totem BattleMech has been going extict faster than replacement parts could be found or salvaged. This and other breakthroughs in 'Mech development have increased the survivability of these ancient designs.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Luthien</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Illician Lancers elect new commanding officer</headline><!-- Source: Mercenaries Supplemental -->
		<date>3046</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>A new commander has been elected by the Elders of the famous mercenary unit. Following the unit tradition General Ellaine Steward has been replaced by General Brenda Bradley in an election process that is quite unique for mercenary commands. The newly appointed CO wasted no time in setting forth her objectives for the coming years and addressed the troops during a broadcast message early this morning. Stating that she will work towards restoring the traditions and upholding the values that the original founders intended. Best of luck General.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>MercNet</service>
		<location>Outreach</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Heir-Designate missing, Protector announces Day of Mourning</headline><!-- Source: Handbook: Major Periphery States -->
		<date>3046-07-11</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Felix Calderon, Heir-Designate of the Taurian Concordant was announced as missing following an update on deep space operations near Concordant territory. The Protector has announced a national day of mourning as it appears that the mission has no reported in for several weeks and missed a scheduled resupply rendevous. So far no additional information is available and sources inside of the government are remaining silent on the mattter. Jeffery Calderon, the fifth in line is expected to be announced as the new Heir-Designate soon after the memorial ceremonies are complete.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Taurus</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>New aerospace fighter enters production</headline><!-- Source: MUL Online -->
		<date>3046</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Wangker Aerospace has recently announced the availability of a new fighter design, the <em>Banshee</em>. Pilots and critics everywhere are wondering about the naming of this new fighter after a BattleMech with such a spotty reputation for being underarmed and outclassed by some BattleMechs half its weight. The new fighter has several technologies based around comfort for pilots during combat maneuvers and the CEO of Wangker stated that it is one of the most advanced fighters currently available.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Axton</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Buda Imperial announces new Tokugawas</headline><!-- Source: Technical Readout: 3058 Upgrade -->
		<date>3046</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The <em>Tokugawa Heavy Tank</em> has resumed production at the Buda Imperial Vehicles (BIV) site on Luthien. While not yet extinct, the limited numbers of vehicles left operational have become so rare that many soldiers went their entire career without ever seeing one. The DCMS has recently announced that their partnership the BIV has increased the number of vehicles significantly and will soon resume in numbers allowing the company to sell limited numbers to non-Kurita forces.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Luthien</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>AFFC stands up new Regimental Combat Team</headline><!-- Source: Field Manual: 3085 -->
		<date>3047</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The 11th FedCom RCT was officially activated late last month on Skye with Hauptmann General Amos Harrington as the commanding officer. Military public relations personnel have been fighting a battle themselves as several more extreme media outlets have called the formation of this unit a ploy to maintain control over a rebellious Combine population. With the rebellion of 3034 still fresh in the minds of many, this unit will have its work cut out with riots and garrison missions throughout the region.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Skye</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Pingree attacked, defenders rally</headline><!-- Source: Field Manual: Free Worlds League -->
		<date>3047-03-01</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The FWLM repulsed an attack earlier this year by the AFFC. The 5th Fusiliers of Oriente commander spoke to media outlets indicating his respect for the men and women that gave their lives to maintain control of the planet and to state that while bloodied they are still more than capable of repelling any further aggression from the Federated Commonwealth. This attack is yet another indication of the instability of the political climate in the region. Reports from sources on the planet are also indicating that several BattleMech designs that have not previously been seen were part of the success of the Fusilier defense. No official announcements have been made regarding this rumor at this time.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Pingree</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>More Centurions on the way</headline><!-- Source: Technical Readout: 3050 Upgrade -->
		<date>3047</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>An agreement between Corean Enterprises and Jalastar Aerospace has recently gone public for the production of <em>Centurion</em> BattleMechs. This agreement has both companies increasing their production lines ensuring that many more of the medium 'Mechs will be produced in the future. Current pilots have to be excited as parts for the older models were becoming more and more difficult to find as the machines were lost.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>New Avalon</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Achernar revisits ancient BattleMech</headline><!-- Source: Technical Readout: 3050 Revised -->
		<date>3047</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Recently announcing the update of the venerable <em>Dervish</em> BattleMech, Achernar BattleMechs has increased their stock holdings by an order of magnitude. Designated the <em>DV-7D</em>, several new technologies have been used to improve on a rather lackluster base model. The change in both the internal structure materials as well as the new armor has several technical companies offering to retrain technicians to repair these rediscovered components. Additional safety measures and ammunition efficiency technologies have also been added to help keep the machines on the field longer than previous variants.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>New Avalon</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Tragedy strikes AFFC</headline><!-- Needs Canonicity check -->
		<date>3047-07-01</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>AFFC public relations staff are currently in the process of selecting a new commander for the 5th Federated Commonwealth Regimental Combat Team after the apparent suicide of their commanding officer. Sources inside the AFFC have stated that there are several candidates but that the current situation has placed Hauptmann General James White as the interim commander until an official announcement is to be made. This is just the latest bad luck for the unit since its formation in 3037. Several other accidents have left the unit a reputation as unlucky and many soldiers have stated that they would rather retire than be assigned to the 5th.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Tsitsang</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Elite technicians form new company: Contracted to Wolf's Dragoons immediately</headline><!-- Source: Field Manual: Mercenaries -->
		<date>3047</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>A group of some of the most skilled scroungers, jury-riggers, technicians, engineers, and tinkerers has come together to form one of the most in-demand working groups on Outreach, 'Mech Magic, Inc. The group has been around for quite some time working as individuals for-hire to almost every mercenary unit that could afford their services. Early this month the company was registered in the ComStar database as one of the first non-mercenary unit formations on the planet. Almost as soon as the company was founded, Colonel Jamie Wolf announced that they would be hiring a majority of the technical staff for the Dragoons. If they had been a traded company their stock would have tripled at the announcement. With a name like that they must have some secret spells working and some of the most damaged 'Mechs come out of their hangars smelling like they just came off the assembly line.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>MercNet</service>
		<location>Outreach</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Noisiel first inaugural Summer Games held: Father versus son to highlight the Games</headline><!-- Source: Mercenaries Supplemental II -->
		<date>3047-07</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Spectators were treated to a new form of 'Mech competition last month on Noisiel. Duke Michael Alextep and his son William faced off in the first ever <em>Atlas</em> rugby match. The event was the highlight of the first annual Noisiel Summer Games announced earlier this year. The event highlighted traditional athletes as well as some of the finest aerobatic maneuvers from AFFC pilots. The event was so popular talks are already under way as to the next years eventy with several ideas being submitted to the Duke's offices.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Noisiel</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Larsha attacked by mercenary force, defeated by garrison forces</headline><!-- Source: Close Quarters -->
		<date>3047-08-15</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Last month a mercenary force calling itself the Seventeenth Recon Regiment attacked a compound on Larsha. The local garrison forces were able to repel the attack and several of the mercenaries were tried under piracy laws and punished according to His Divine Wisdom. Let this stand as a message that any further incursions into the Capellan Confederation, all citizens stand willing to repel their forces.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CBC</service>
		<location>Larsha</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>The Bounty Hunters breaks records!</headline><!-- Source: Interstellar Players -->
		<date>3047-09</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>A new holovid series recently released in the FWL has broken all prime time viewer records. Based on the myth of the Bounty Hunter, the series has captured the attention of several Inner Sphere production companies who are said to be interested in securing the movie rights. Another record that the series has broken is the most pirated holovid in the Inner Sphere in the last 200 years.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Atreus</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Kali Yama Industries facilities damaged during raid</headline><!-- Source: Field Manual: Free Worlds League -->
		<date>3047</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Reports from Kalidasa media indicate that a siege of the Kali Yama facilities occured late last week. The announcement by the company of advanced technical discoveries and the improvement of several BattleMech chassis is believed to have been the reason for this attack. The raid lasted for several hours as the Silver Hawk Irregulars attempted to take the facility back from Harlock's Warriors. Ground crews are working to repair damage to the facility while technical and legal staff work to discover what was taken. Sources indicate that several crates of equipment were taken from the facility and loaded onto vehicles before the defending units could mobilize to engage them. Officials in the FWLM are rumored to be looking at replacing the local commander in light of this raid.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Kalidasa</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Archenar BattleMechs specs leak for new variant of classic design</headline><!-- Source: MUL Online -->
		<date>3048</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The Helm Memory core has allowed another design to become even more effective. The latest variant of the <em>Phoenix Hawk</em> is flush with new bells and whistles that would make General Kerensky himself envious. Details are still coming in but a source has leaked that the new <em>PXH-3D</em> has not only incredible range for its weaponry, but that is also has been redesigned from the ground up to be more effective as a medium scout far from supply lines.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>FCNS</service>
		<location>New Avalon</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Axman unveiled</headline><!-- Source: MUL Online -->
		<date>3048</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Today the Federated Commonwealth unveiled a brand new design, developed by Team Banzai and the NAIS, the new <em>Axman</em> is the follow up to the iconic <em>Hatchetman</em> BattleMech. The new <em>Axman</em> weighs significantly more than its predecessor but is otherwise very similar. Both 'Mechs wield massive hatchets and are armed with large-bore autocannons for destroying other 'Mechs and both designs have a top speed of nearly 65 km/h and jump jets. The biggest difference between the <em>Axman</em> and the <em>Hatchetman</em>, other than their size, is the inclusion of rediscovered Lostech on the <em>Axman</em>.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>FBC</service>
		<location>New Avalon</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Rim Collection Charter signed</headline><!-- Source: Handbook: Major Periphery States -->
		<date>3048-05-14</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>CNB has just received news from the Periphery that six former Rim Worlds Republic planets have signed the Rim Collection Charter. The Charter bands these six planets together into a mutual defensive pact and the six member states hope their alliance will allow them to better defend against pirate predation and pool their resources to improve the conditions on their planets.<br><br>Speaking on behalf of the new Periphery nation, Planetary Councilman Roberts explained the new nation’s goals to “Improve the living conditions for the residents of the Rim Collection planets, through improved security, pooling resources, and expanding trade with neighboring nations.”</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Gillfillan's Gold</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Devastator unveiled</headline><!-- Source: MUL Online -->
		<date>3048</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The Federated Commonwealth unveiled a new construction line at the Norse-Storm manufacturing plant on Loxley today. A news conference held at the plant wowed reports by showing off the impressive <em>Devastator</em> assault 'Mech.<br><br>The <em>Devastator</em> is rumored to have been designed by Aleksander Kerensky himself, just prior to the Amaris Coup, which resulted in only a handful of prototypes ever making it off the factory floor before the design was lost to history. The <em>Devastator</em> wasn't rediscovered until forces from the Federated Suns discovered blueprints in an abandoned Star League facility on Hoff in 3023. Unfortunately, the advanced materials and parts required meant that the <em>Devastator</em> would not see production for another two decades, with full production only beginning earlier this year.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>FCNS</service>
		<location>Loxley</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Avenger DropShip upgraded</headline><!-- Source: Technical Readout: 3057 -->
		<date>3048-11-02</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Today the Federated Commonwealth unveiled the first of many upgrades to the realm's DropShip fleet. The first <em>Avenger</em>-class assault DropShip has completed an upgrade using rediscovered weapon and cooling systems to greatly increase its combat effectiveness. The Commonwealth Admiralty reports that they expect upgrades to begin over the next few years of all Commonwealth DropShips and JumpShips.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>FCNS</service>
		<location>Delavan</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Creation of 11th and 12th FedCom RCTs announced</headline>
		<date>3049-01-05</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Announced to much fanfare, the Armed Forces of the Federated Commonwealth christened two new regimental combat teams; the 11th and 12th Federated Commonwealth RCTs will be stationed on Skye and Marcus respectively. The new commands are staffed by soldiers from throughout the Federated Commonwealth and will assist in the defense of the Sarna March.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>FCNS</service>
		<location>Marcus</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>New BattleMech variant unveiled</headline><!-- Source: MUL Online -->
		<date>3049</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>A new variant of the <em>Axeman</em> BattleMech has been demonstrated to the top brass of the AFFC. The new variant changes the entire tactical purpose of the 'Mech more inline with standoff fighters such as the <em>Trebuchet</em>. Long range missle systems are added in place of the devastating heavy autocannon which can literally tear many 'Mechs to scrap before the massive hand-to-hand weapon can be used to finish them off. Many veteran MechWarriors are leery though of having the heavier weapon removed in favor of such a long-range focused design. Time and experience will tell if they are proven to be valid concerns.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>FNS</service>
		<location>Furillo</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Periphery gone quiet</headline>
		<date>3049-12-10</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>For almost four months now, the Periphery realms Elysian Fields, the Oberon Confederation, Greater Valkyrate and the Baron of Strang have all been silent. While not overly unusual due to the limited collection of HPG's in that corner of the galaxy and their limited trade with the Inner Sphere, there have been worrying reports along the border of the Federated Commonwealth and Free Rasalhague Republic that there have been refugees fleeing from some unknown attackers. While most news sources are claiming it is nothing more than a new pirate lord or simply a war between the various minor realms, the Observer is not so sure. Having spoken with several refugees, they claim that the attackers were far too organized and were using unrecognizable equipment. What does that leave us? Has the Federated Commonwealth decided it is time to capture the way-ward pirate-realms of their near-Periphery or is this the start of something far more sinister?</p>]]></desc>
		<service>INO</service>
		<location>Winfield</location>
	</newsItem>
<!-- Clan Invasion Era (3050 - 3061) -->
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Ecological disaster prompts scientific warnings</headline> <!-- Source: Touring the Stars: Benet III -->
		<date>305X</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Scientists are coming together this week to discuss the current status of Benet III. The planet, known for its seismic and volcanic activity, has recently seen in increase in the amount and frequency of outgassing. The most recent incident caused several injuries and has rendered an area just outside of Donner uninhabitable. Some scientists are already calling for massive evacuations of some regions based on samples taken in the most active areas.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Benet III</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Dustball losing its customers</headline><!-- Source: Objective Raids -->
		<date>3051</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>An order straight from the AFFC command is blacklisting Dustball for all service members. The memo released to media outlets indicates that the proximity to the front lines and danger to visiting personnel are the primary reasons for this action. It is currently unclear why the AFFC command chose to isolate a single world instread of listing the region. Sources believe that the resorts on the planet that cater to more carnal desires may be the actual reason for this decision.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>DBC</service>
		<location>Donegal</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Cats coughing up furballs after facing dragons and hounds</headline><!-- Source: Luthien -->
		<date>3052-02</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Filed 07 January 3052</p><p>Clan forces attempted to take the heart of the Draconis Combine but were repelled with heavy losses by a combined mercenary and DCMS force. Reports from embedded correspondents indicate that two Clans, the Smoke Jaguars and the Nova Cats dropped hundreds of BattleMech and powered infantry forces. The defenders, DCMS and famed units such as the Kell Hounds and Wolf's Dragoons along with several other attached companies stalled and then routed the Clan forces in what could prove to be one of the bloodiest battles in the invasion so far. Casualties on all sides are estimated to be in the thousands as numbers come in from the front. On both sides of the field, several new chassis have been recorded in action and DCMS forces have reportedly salvaged a significant number of Clan BattleMechs.</p><p>The mercenaries involved were last recorded to be employed by the Federated Commonwealth and no word has yet been made as to the continued status of that contract or the addition of a new contract for the typically anti-Dragoons Combine.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>MercNet</service>
		<location>Luthien</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Major news network dissolved</headline><!-- Source: Field Manual: Updates -->
		<date>3052-05-10</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Following the treachery of personnel within the ComStar organization, several departments within the organization have been dissolved. One of these, the ComStar News Bureau, was recently reformatted into the Interstellar News Network. This new service was developed with accurate reporting in mind and will have independent reporters accross the Inner Sphere providing the latest news. Todays braodcast is sponsored by Pop-Cola, the only drink for Solaris Champions.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>INN</service>
		<location>Terra</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>ComStar questions accuracy of Draconis Warlord statements</headline><!-- Source: ComStar -->
		<date>3053</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>A recent interview with Warlord Scoble of the DCMS brought to light some statements that ComStar is challenging in the open press. The origins of the MRB or Mercenary Review Board has long been seen as a part of ComStar history but the Warlord has stated that the Draconis Combine is responsible for forcing the hand of ComStar after a mercenary unit violated their contract. At this time it appears that ComStar is only working to dispute the claim and has not taken any censorship actions to prevent the viewing of the interview.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>FWNA</service>
		<location>Stewartson</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>DCMS soldier memoir released outside of Draconis Combine</headline><!-- Source: Clantroops -->
		<date>3053</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Dragon Press house recently released a book authorized by the DCMS that contained accounts of events during the initial Clan invasion. While many of the accounts are from areas already covered in detail by other books, the view from the line soldiers of the Draconis Combine are seldom seen due to strict publication and censorship laws. <em>A Lucky Star</em> is expected to be available across the Inner Sphere in a matter of months as the publishing house struggles to keep up with the demand.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>INN</service>
		<location>Luthien</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Holobook describes battle for Luthien in gory detail</headline><!-- Source: Luthien -->
		<date>3054</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The most recent holobook covering the battle for Luthien has hit the market with mixed reviews. Soldiers and other military personnel have come out in favor of the detail that the author put into the descriptions of the battle. Some reviews call into question the need for such graphic detail, calling <em>Tracks in the Sand: The Battle of Luthien</em> little more than an attempt to capitalize on shock value with no regard to the human losses.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>INN</service>
		<location>Outreach</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Relive the Battle of Luthien and other turning points</headline><!-- Source: Luthien -->
		<date>3054</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Virtual Arts Simulations has recently released a simulation package compatible with most training pods that allow users to enter several key battles of the Clan Invasion. While some are calling this little more than a macabre exercise, at least one mercenary CO has stated that this simulation is one of the best tools to show how even a force with a technological or experience advantage can be defeated using sound tactical choices.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>FNS</service>
		<location>New Avalon</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Waco accuses Dragoons of treason</headline><!-- Source: Mercenary's Handbook 3055 -->
		<date>3054-08</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Filed 10 July 3054</p><p>In a recent interview on Outreach, Colonel Wayne Waco made statements accusing the Wolf's Dragoons of treason against the Inner Sphere. Naming several members of the famed mercenary unit and their charges he discussed instances and inconsistencies with their past contracts. No word on if the Dragoons will make any comments of their own but it is known that Colonel Waco has never seen eye-to-eye since a contract in 3008 pit the two mercenary units against one another resulting in the death of Colonel Waco's son.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>MercNet</service>
		<location>Outreach</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Wolf autobiography makes best seller list in record time</headline><!-- Source: Mercenary's Handbook 3055 -->
		<date>3055</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>A recently published autobiography written by famed mercenary Jamie Wolf has made the best sellers list in the Federated Commonwealth in just two weeks after initial publication. Titled <em>A Lifetime in the Trade: Reminiscences of a Mercenary</em>, it covers the personal and unit history of Colonel Wolf and the Dragoons themselves. Readers across the Inner Sphere have come to know the Dragoons from their exploits and scandals and some would even call them as infamous as they are revered.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>INN</service>
		<location>Outreach</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>New book provides insight on battle for Luthien</headline><!-- Source: Luthien -->
		<date>3055</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Yoshinobu Tsetsuhara and Luthien Publishing have released a new book covering several conflicts during the Clan Invasion. The book, <em>The Killing Doves: Friends of the Dragon at War</em> provides a unique perspective on how the DCMS works with other forces and how honor plays an important part in those interactions.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>INN</service>
		<location>Luthien</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Draconis Combine questions accuracy of new title</headline><!-- Source: Luthien -->
		<date>3055</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>A new book titled <em>The Dragon and the Cat: A History of the Draconis Combine in the Clan Invasion</em> has stirred some controversy in the Draconis Combine for its descriptions of units and battles. Any mention of Combine personnel acting less than honorably or failing to meet their enemy has been denied by several notable historians while any instance of absolute victory, even if questionable, has been held as truth.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>INN</service>
		<location>Buckminster</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Noisiel Hiring Hall hosts first rounds of hiring during open house</headline><!-- Source: Mercenaries Supplemental II -->
		<date>3055</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>With the challenges of a broad Inner Sphere and the Clan Occupation Zone cutting many mercenary forces off from traditional Hiring Halls, the government of Noisiel has officially opened their Hall. While not as state-of-the-art as the facilities on Outreach, the new facility houses several floors of offices and work areas for potential negotiations and R&R.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>MercNet</service>
		<location>Noisiel</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Draconis Combine files breach of contract for mercenary force</headline><!-- Source: Far Country --><!-- Canon, Tetatae approved -->
		<date>3056-12</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Filed 10 November 3056</p><p>The mercenary force registered as Vost Lance is hereby chared with breach of contract and piracy. On or about 07 November 3056, the JumpShip <em>Telendine</em> was hijacked by the mercenaries and has not been seen in the Salford system. Any information regarding this incident should be reported to the MRBC or the local Draconis Combine representative. Vost Lance is considered to be Wanted as of this announcement.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>MercNet</service>
		<location>Outreach</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Operation Guerrero ends</headline>
		<date>3058-01-01</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The Federated Commonwealth breathes a sigh of relief as word spreads that hostilities between our nation and the Free Worlds League and their Capellan Confederation allies have come to an end after several months of brutal fighting. To say the Federated Commonwealth has had a rough year would be a major understatement; following allegations that First Prince Victor Ian Steiner-Davion ordered Joshua Marik, heir to the Free Worlds League, replaced with a body-double while he was being treated at the New Avalon Institute of Science, the First Prince's sister Katrina Steiner-Davion removed the Lyran half of the realm from the long standing alliance two days after the Capellan Confederation and Free Worlds League used the alleged crimes of the First Prince as grounds to launch an invasion. On September 16th, the Capellan Confederation and the Free Worlds League launched a massive invasion of our realm, striking planets captured nearly 30 years ago during the 4th Succession War. Peace was formally declared between the Federated Commonwealth, Free Worlds League and Capellan Confederation on December 15th, 3057.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>NANS</service>
		<location>New Avalon</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>War between Clans?</headline>
		<date>3058-01-02</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Our new agency has been receiving whispers and rumors of a massive battle in the Clan Invasion Corridor between the Jade Falcons and the Wolves. As always, news from the conquered territory is scarce at best, however from what we have heard both Clans have been fighting on multiple worlds, though the reasons behind the conflict are at this time unknown. Perhaps this large-scale infighting between the Clan invaders will allow the governments of the Inner Sphere to finally remove the rampaging Clan hordes once and for all.<br><br>Once piece of news that we have received from the fighting is that the notorious Black Widow, Natasha Kerensky, was killed in combat on the planet Twycross. We have received no details of how the fearsome femme fatale died, other than that she “went down in a blaze of glory”. This ends the legend half a century in the making.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>INN</service>
		<location>Arc-Royal</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Inner Sphere in conflict</headline>
		<date>3058-03-15</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Low-level conflict abounds across the Inner Sphere. Reports are flooding in from each realm of worlds invaded or unrest; although none of the Successor States are in open warfare, except the Lyran Alliance which has suffered a major Jade Falcon invasion.<br><br>The next biggest hotbed by far is the Federated Commonwealth's Sarna March, which is now being called the Chaos March. After the recent Free Worlds League and Capellan Confederation invasion shattered the March's defenses dozens of planets have found themselves with no centralized authority and the result has been chaos. The entire area is experiencing or in fear of riots, pirates, and raids from minor neighbors and superpowers alike. However, several planets have banded together in mutual defense to form several new minor-powers, such as the Tall Trees Alliance and the resurrected Sarna Supremacy, which was originally conquered centuries ago by the Confederation. The violence has even grown to include Towne as forces from the Draconis Combine vie for supremacy and endanger the nearly decade long peace that the Federated Commonwealth has enjoyed with its once bitter enemy.<br><br>As the March descends into anarchy, even surrounding planets are being swept into the whirlwind. Terra, the birthplace of humanity, is currently the site of a brutal battle between ComStar and the Word of Blake. Details are almost non-existent but INN has learned that ComStar forces on planet are all but defeated and the Word of Blake will soon be returning home.<br><br>But by far, the most overt fighting is taking place along the Lyran Alliance border with Clan Jade Falcon. Shortly after we received word that the fighting between Clans Wolf and Jade Falcon had ended, the Jade Falcons began a vicious invasion of the Lyran Alliance; hitting multiple planets and ultimately driving for Coventry, a major manufacturing center for the Alliance. However, the planet is well defended and so far the Falcon's invasion has bogged down after landing on the planet. Reports indicate extensive losses for the Lyran forces initially defending the planet, the arrival of a mercenary coalition, hired by the Alliance and led by the Wolfs Dragoons is all that kept the planet from falling to the Falcons. Will the Alliance lose one of its manufacturing gems or will the Falcons break their beak on the tenacious Inner Sphere defenders?</p>]]></desc>
		<service>INN</service>
		<location>Bryant</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>FWLM launches new WarShips</headline>
		<date>3058-05-05</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The FWLM has announced the launch of the first of two new lines of WarShips. The first is the 485,000 ton <em>Impavido</em>-class destroyer and the second is the massive 815,000 ton <em>Agamemnon</em>-class heavy cruiser. At least one ship from each class has already finished production or will finish production in the next week. The Free Worlds League is a safer place with the addition of these new stalwart defenders.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>MCT</service>
		<location>Atreus</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Jade Falcons defeated on Coventry</headline>
		<date>3058-06-23</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The Jade Falcon threat has finally been removed from Coventry, thanks to the arrival of a multi-national task force. Months of bitter fighting for the planet ended peacefully when, shortly after the task force landed, the defenders and the Falcons met for peace talks. Due to the show of strength from the multi-national force, the Jade Falcons agreed to leave the system with no further fighting. This puts an end to more than three months of intense-combat for the manufacturing jewel and also brings an end to the massive Jade Falcon invasion. The multi-national coalition, led by First Prince Victor Davion, inspired Archon Katrina Steiner to invite the other nations of the Inner Sphere to a peace conference, scheduled for October 1st, to further peaceful relations between the realms of the Inner Sphere and to counteract the Clan threat that hangs over everyone.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>TBC</service>
		<location>Tharkad</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Capellan Confederation launches Feng Huang cruiser</headline>
		<date>3058-08-02</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Today, the Capellan nation celebrates the launch of the first <em>Feng Huang</em>-class cruiser. The mighty WarShip weighs 970,000 tons and is large enough to take on almost any ship in existence. His Celestial Wisdom was present for the christening of this new ship and proclaimed it one of “many to come” in the next several years.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CBC</service>
		<location>Sian</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Sirian Lancers reclaim Sirius and Procyon</headline>
		<date>3058-09-28</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The Globe has received reports that forces from the Sirian Lancers have ventured into the "Chaos March" to reclaim their lost homes of Sirius and Procyon after both planets failed to be reclaimed during Operation Guerrero last year. While the Lancers are rumored to have acted without orders from the FWLM, the Sirian Brigade released a statement that they felt compelled to "secure their homes and loved ones that were stolen away nearly three decades ago and keep their home safe from the ravages of the Chaos March." The Globe has received no response from Atreus when we inquired on the Captain-General's view of the situation. Regardless, we at the Globe are happy to welcome our brothers and sisters from Sirius and Procyon back into the League.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>GB</service>
		<location>Marik</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Whitting Conference begins</headline>
		<date>3058-10-01</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Today marks the start of the Whitting Conference, called by Archon Katrina Steiner to foster peaceful relations between the realms of the Inner Sphere and to end the Clan threat for good. The Whitting Conference is named for the small village on Coventry where a coalition of forces from each Inner Sphere nation conducted peace talks with the Khan of the invading Jade Falcons. Talks have only just begun but the Inner Sphere holds its breath in hope for a future of peace after centuries of war.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>INN</service>
		<location>Tharkad</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Coordinator nearly assassinated?</headline>
		<date>3058-10-12</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Unconfirmed reports are running rampant through the Combine and the Voice of the Dragon won't report them; on July 1st during the Coordinator's birthday ceremony forces of the DCMS attempted to kill the Dragon, Theodore Kurita himself. While word has been stifled by the Voice of the Dragon and the ISF, the Drake has received word that the traitorous attacks by supposedly loyal Combine soldiers were only stopped by the mercenary 17th Recon Regiment, better known as Camacho's Caballeros. Does this attack suggest deeper problems within the Combine? Can the forces of the DCMS be trusted to defend us or are they too busy with their own personal honor to defend the people of the Combine?</p>]]></desc>
		<service>Drake</service>
		<location>Luthien</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Star League reformed</headline>
		<date>3058-11-21</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Today, the Lords and Great Houses of the Inner Sphere have set aside their petty bickering and power mongering to usher in a new age of peace. This morning, the Lords of the Capellan Confederation, Draconis Combine, Federated Commonwealth, Free Worlds League, Lyran Alliance, Free Rasalhague Republic, and the St. Ives Compact signed the Constitution of the Second Star League with the blessings of ComStar.</p><p>The first act of the Second Star League, reformed after centuries, was to elect a new First Lord. The hostess of the Whitting Conference, Archon Katrina Steiner, started elections by nominating Chancellor Sun-Tzu Liao of the Capellan Confederation and voting passed nearly unanimously to name the leader of the Capellan Confederation First Lord of the Star League.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>INN</service>
		<location>Tharkad</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Formation of Tamar Cavaliers Regiment announced</headline>
		<date>3058-12-12</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Earlier today, Duke Robert Kelswa-Steiner raised a new regiment to join his House Guard, the Tamar Cavaliers. Duke Kelswa-Steiner publicly stated that the intended purpose for the new Cavaliers is to one day see Tamar and the rest of the Tamar Pact rescued from Clan tyranny and returned to the Lyran Alliance. Duke Kelswa Steiner has generously given direct command of the unit to Lyran High Command for the defense of their border with Clans Jade Falcon and Wolf.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>SNN</service>
		<location>Skye</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Commando BattleMech updated</headline>
		<date>3058-01-18</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Today officials from the Lyran Alliance Armed Forces announced the release of the latest variant of the venerable <em>Commando</em> BattleMech line, the new COM-7S, which utilizes cutting edge technology to improve the survivability and firepower of the mainstay light 'Mech of the LAAF.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>TBC</service>
		<location>Tharkad</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>George Hasek II named Director of the Capellan March</headline>
		<date>3059-03-28</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Citing Duke Morgan Hasek-Davion's expanded role in the newly reformed Star League Defense Force, earlier today his son George Michael Hasek was named Director of the Capellan March. This elevation of George Hasek makes him Duke of the Capellan March in all but name, giving him control of all of the Marches military forces and burdening him with the defense of the entire March. While George Hasek is young, he has shown promise since his graduation from the Sakhara Academy and his father, Duke Morgan Hasek-Davion, has declared that he has the utmost faith in his son's ability and judgment.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>NSNS</service>
		<location>New Syrtis</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Operation Bulldog a "success"</headline>
		<date>3059-06-18</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>During a press conference today, First Lord Sun-Tzu Liao announced that on May 20th, the Star League began a massive invasion, dubbed Operation Bulldog, aimed at the complete removal of Clan Smoke Jaguar forces from the Inner Sphere. This undertaking is being conducted by a massive multi-national force led Archon-Prince Victor Steiner-Davion of the Federated Commonwealth and legendary Precentor Martial Anastasius Focht. Forces from all member states of the reborn Star League are taking part in this massive invasion and the First Lord reports that the invasion so far has been a massive success, with battles progressing faster and significantly fewer casualties than anticipated.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>INN</service>
		<location>Sian</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Clan Nova Cat joins the Star League Defense Force</headline>
		<date>3059-08-25</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Press conferences from the Star League Defense Force indicate that the war against the Smoke Jaguars is progressing well and stated that Clan Nova Cat has joined the reformed Star League. This unexpected support frees up dozens of regiments for the battle with the Smoke Jaguars and all but assures that they will be unable to withstand the combined strength of the Second Star League.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>INN</service>
		<location>Luthien</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Operation Bulldog stalling</headline>
		<date>3059-12-02</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>News from the front reports that Operation Bulldog's progress has slowed. While the operation made massive inroads into Smoke Jaguar territory in the opening months while the Clanners were caught off balance, they have since redoubled their defenses and have slowed the advances of the new Star League Defense Force. However, First Lord Sun-Tzu Liao restated his confidence in the SLDF and praised their valiant efforts and assured all people of the Inner Sphere that the war would not end until the Smoke Jaguars were defeated once and for all.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>Luthien</service>
		<location>INN</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>First Lord meeting with Periphery neighbors?</headline>
		<date>3060-02-03</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Reports from the Taurian Concordat suggest that First Lord and Chancellor Sun-Tzu Liao is planning a meeting with Magistrix Emma Centrella from the Magistracy of Canopus and Protector of the Realm Jeffrey Calderon from the Taurian Concordat to discuss a potential alliance. What could this mean for the future of our realm? The meddling of Inner Sphere powers has led to nothing but ruin for our realm in the past.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>TBC</service>
		<location>Taurus</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Formation of 2nd Janissaries Brigade announced</headline>
		<date>3060-06-01</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Today, the St. Ives Compact celebrates the creation of the 2nd Janissaries Brigade. The 2nd Janissaries are a combined arms brigade formed along the principles of the Federated Suns' regimental combat teams with a regiment of BattleMechs supported by multiple regiments of conventional armor, infantry, artillery, and aerospace forces. The 2nd Janissaries mean a safer St. Ives and a more secure future for our Compact.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>SIBC</service>
		<location>St. Ives</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>New Diverse Optics factory opens</headline>
		<date>3060-06-28</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Today the Combine celebrates not only the continued success of the Draconis Combine Mustered Soldiery and our allies fighting valiantly to destroy the threat of the evil Smoke Jaguars forever, but also the improvement of our great nation's powerful defense industries. Earlier today Irian BattleMechs Unlimited officially opened a new branch of Diverse Optics on the planet of Kessel. Diverse Optics are one of the Inner Sphere's premier creators of all types of laser weaponry and the new plant on Kessel will be making top of the line models, ensuring our warriors have only the best tools to defend the Dragon.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>VotD</service>
		<location>Kessel</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Misrule in the Federated Suns</headline>
		<date>3060-07-17</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Reports continue to trickle into the Lyran Alliance from our old sister state the Federated Suns indicating growing discontent with Regent Yvonne Steiner-Davion. The people of the realm continue to suffer under the poor economy and report it continues to grow harder and harder to acquire even the most basic essentials as shipping and jobs are disrupted. There have also been reports of protests on multiple planets demanding change.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>AP</service>
		<location>Tharkad</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Alarion Military Academy opens</headline>
		<date>3060-08-15</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Today, the Lyran Alliance Armed Forces (LAAF) held the opening ceremony for their newest military academy. The new military academy will focus on training crews, technicians and pilots of the LAAF's expanding WarShip, JumpShip, DropShip and aerospace fighter fleet. The Alarion Military Academy has attracted some exceptionally skilled and experienced staff to ensure that our next generations of naval officers and enlisted have the best training available to keep the Alliance safe from any enemy.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>DBC</service>
		<location>Alarion</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Coventry Military Academy reopens</headline>
		<date>3060-08-16</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>We have more good news to report regarding the Lyran Alliance's military academies. A ceremony was just held to christen the reopening of the Coventry Military Academy. As all of our viewers recall, the Coventry Military Academy was damaged during the Jade Falcons' destructive invasion in 3058, which saw the Jade Falcons conquer several worlds before converging on Coventry with several Galaxies of 'Mechs. The Falcons were intent on capturing the planet's vital 'Mech factories and there was fierce fighting by the defending 10th Skye Rangers, Coventry Militia and the Coventry Military Academy Training Cadre. The Academy's buildings and grounds were caught in the middle of one particularly violent battle and the Academy has been rebuilding ever since the Falcons were forced off the planet.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>DBC</service>
		<location>Coventry</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Discontent in the Federated Suns</headline>
		<date>3060-09-18</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Our correspondents in the Federated Suns continue to report on the rising discontent with the rule of Regent Yvonne Steiner-Davion have spilled over into full blown riots on several planets. These riots are expected to make a bad situation worse by slowing the shipment of food and other every day essentials. Polls indicate the vast majority of citizens in the Federated Suns feel Yvonne is doing a poor job of running the realm in her brother Victor's absence.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>AP</service>
		<location>Tharkad</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Hustaing attacked, Chancellor missing</headline>
		<date>3060-10-02</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>CBC has just received news that the Blackwind Lancers, a battalion from the St. Ives Compact, launched a surprise raid on the Confederation planet of Hustaing on September 26. We have very little information to report at this time as the Word of Blake has placed the planet under a temporary blackout and is not sending or receiving any HPG messages for Hustaing. Reports indicate that First Lord of the Star League and Chancellor of the Capellan Confederation, his Celestial Wisdom Sun-Tzu Liao and his fiancé Duchess Isis Marik were scheduled to make an appearance on Hustaing the day of the attack and there have been no sightings of the Chancellor since the attack and no official word from Sian. We here at CBC hope the Celestial Wisdom is safe and this situation will be cleared up shortly.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CBC</service>
		<location>Sian</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Detroit Conference attacked</headline>
		<date>3060-10-31</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Disaster struck today at the Detroit Conference. The conference, attended by Protector Jeffrey Calderon and Magistrix Emma Centralla and representatives of the Capellan Confederation, due to the Chancellor's uncertain status after the attack on Hustaing, were planning to discuss a potential alliance between the three realms. Unfortunately, President Sherman Maltin and several of the Colonial Marshals have taken the Protector and Magistrex hostage in a bid for independence for the Concordat's New Colony Region. For now the situation is tense as forces from the Capellan Confederation, Magistracy of Canopus and Taurian Concordat struggle to respond.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>TPBC</service>
		<location>Detroit</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Clan Ghost Bear here to stay</headline>
		<date>3060-11-01</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>For the first time ever, a Clan Khan, specifically Khan Bjorn Jorgensson of Clan Ghost Bear, invited journalists from across the Inner Sphere to the Ghost Bear Inner Sphere capital Alshain for a press conference. During the conference the Khan announced his Clans intention to become permanent residents of the Inner Sphere and the formation of the “Ghost Bear Dominion”. Stating that the “Clan Crusade” was a failure and the Ghost Bears have decided it is time to “work towards increased cooperation between the warriors of the Clan and the citizens of our new holdings and our neighbors”. It is unclear what the formation of the new Dominion truly means for the people of the Dominion and its neighbors, however the Ghost Bear Khan expressed an interest in making the Dominion more open to the Inner Sphere than in the past, including expanded trade, especially with the nascent Free Rasalhague Republic, which has close ties to the populations on most of the captured Ghost Bear planets.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>INN</service>
		<location>Alshain</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Chancellor safe</headline>
		<date>3060-11-05</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Today is a day of celebration for people of the Confederation, CBC has finally received word from the planet of Hustaing and along with verification that First Lord of the Star League and our Celestial Wisdom, Chancellor Sun-Tzu Liao is safe and never landed on Hustaing. The Blackwind Lancers threatened his Celestial Wisdom's fiance, Duchess Marik, but she was kept safe from the vile Lancers by the valiant efforts of the Hustaing Militia and Warrior House Hiritsu, and their righteous fury led to the capture of the vile Lancers and their 'Mechs. The Chancellor has announced the formation of the Hustaing Warriors, a new 'Mech battalion using the 'Mechs captured from the Blackwind Lancers and raised from Hustaing locals.<br><br>In his infinite wisdom, the Chancellor called an emergency meeting with the Star League council and declared a state of emergency and requested peacekeeping forces from the rest of the Inner Sphere to secure and demilitarize the St. Ives border to prevent any further unsanctioned attacks by the aggressive rebellious nation. The peacekeepers are expected to arrive within the next few weeks and I am sure the people of the Confederation will feel safer knowing the mighty Star League will help ensure our safety from our belligerent neighbors.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CBC</service>
		<location>Hustaing</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Star League 'Peacekeepers' occupy St. Ives Compact</headline>
		<date>3060-12-02</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Reports indicate that the first wave of “Star League Peacekeepers” have arrived in the St. Ives Compact at the behest of First Lord Liao. Five planets have been targeted for 'demilitarization' including Indicass, Vestallas, Nashuar, Brighton and Denbar. Units from the Free Worlds League, Draconis Combine, Lyran Alliance, Capellan Confederation, Magistracy of Canopus, Taurian Concordat and even our own Federated Commonwealth have made landfall. There has already been one reported incident, resulting from when a battalion of the 2nd St. Ives Lancers on Indicass, unaware of the 'peacekeepers' intentions, opened fire on the 2nd Oriente Hussars as they unloaded from their DropShips. Reports indicate damage was minimal before the St. Ives forces were ordered to stand down by high command.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>NSB</service>
		<location>New Syrtis</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Archon Katrina Steiner-Davion named Regent of Federated Commonwealth</headline>
		<date>3060-12-22</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>In an unexpected, though welcome, move Yvonne Steiner-Davion held a press conference earlier today and announced she abdicated her position as Regent immediately. Citing the realm's recent unrest, poor economy and the growing discontent that have plagued her short reign while her brother Archon-Prince Victor Steiner-Davion is fighting the Clans in Combine space, Yvonne has named her sister, Archon Katrina Steiner-Davion as her replacement regent for the Federated Commonwealth. Yvonne went on to expand that she had every faith that her older sister Katrina would be able to fix the problems in the Federated Commonwealth and restore the people's faith, pointing out the great success Katrina Steiner-Davion has enjoyed while ruling the Lyran Alliance. After the press conference, reports indicated that the former regent was leaving New Avalon and was headed for an undisclosed location. Archon-Princess Katrina Steiner-Davion held her own press conference immediately after announcing her acceptance of the new position and the great responsibilities that came with it and she thanked her sister for thinking first of the people of the Federated Commonwealth and wished her brother Victor would have remembered those same responsibilities before abandoning the realm for his crusade against the Clans.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>NANS</service>
		<location>New Avalon</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>SLDF Peacekeepers leave St. Ives Compact</headline>
		<date>3061-01-10</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>In a promising turn of events, Duchess Candace Liao has convince the Star League to remove 'peacekeepers' from our border. The forces from all member nations of the Star League were put in place at the behest of First Lord Sun-Tzu Liao and most of them made landfall more than a month ago. Since then, the St. Ives Compact has held its breath as the peacekeepers attempted to disarm our border and defenders. There have been several skirmishes already between the peacekeepers and St. Ives forces. Hopefully with the removal of the Star League forces will defuse the situation. The Star League forces are scheduled to leave the Compact on January 27th.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>SIBC</service>
		<location>St. Ives</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Capellan Confederation invades St. Ives Compact</headline>
		<date>3061-02-05</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>St. Ives is in open war with the Capellan Confederation. Immediately following the removal of the Star League peacekeeping forces, Capellan Confederation forces landed and the invasion truly began. Reports indicate that the Compact has already lost several planets and our defenders struggle to hold back the larger Capellan Confederation. To add additional insult to injury, our 'allies' in the Federated Commonwealth have so far shown no signs of sending additional aid to help defend our realm against the voracious Confederation.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>SIBC</service>
		<location>St. ives</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Trinity Alliance formed</headline>
		<date>3061-02-28</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Earlier this month joint forces from the Capellan Confederation and the Magistracy of Canopus landed on Detroit and attempted to break the hostage situation where New Colony President Sherman Maltin was holding Protector Calderon and Magistrix Centrella. The forces were successful in putting down the revolt and managed to rescue Magistrix Centrella. Unfortunately, both President Maltin and Protector Calderon were killed in the fighting. Already Grover Shraplen has been named the Taurian Concordat's new Protector and reports indicate that the successful joint operation has propelled the 'Trinity Alliance' talks forward. The Capellan Confederation has agreed to a mutual defense pact and has generously offered to send teachers, engineers and technical staff to the Magistracy and Concordat to bring both realms 'into the 31st century'.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>MBC</service>
		<location>Detroit</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Clan Smoke Jaguar defeated</headline>
		<date>3061-05-15</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Breaking news from Luthien. Star League Defense Force General Victor Ian Steiner-Davion has made his first public appearance in well over a year and announced the end of the Clan threat. Reports are only now being made public that Operation Bulldog, the operation to remove the Smoke Jaguars from Inner Sphere space was only the first half of the plan and was completed in a few months in 3059. The rest of the mission, Task Force Serpent, was kept completely classified until now and was a second attack sent directly to the Clan homeworlds to destroy the Smoke Jaguars in their den. This second prong of the attack was led by Duke Morgan Hasek-Davion and General Ariana Winston, commander of the famed SLDF Eridani Light Horse. Reports indicate that both commanders were killed while on the Jaguar homeworld of Huntress, though their mission was ultimately a success when the forces from Operation Bulldog, following the Smoke Jaguar forces fleeing the Inner Sphere, arrived in Clan Space.<br><br>After the Jaguars were completely destroyed, Victor Steiner-Davion led his coalition forces to the Clan's capital world, Strana Mechty, and waged a trial against the Clans to end their invasion for good. Forces from each realm squared off against Clan forces and were ultimately victorious, defeating the Clans by their own rules. The Inner Sphere can breath a collective sigh of relief to know that the Clans' invasion plans have been ended and we may be able to expect peace along that front for the immediate future.<br><br>Unfortunately for Victor Steiner-Davion, he returns home to find himself an Archon Prince without a realm. Just three months ago his youngest sister Yvonne abdicated her regency to their sister Katrina Steiner-Davion. The relationship between Victor and Katrina has reportedly been strained for years, starting with the revelations that Victor attempted to replace Joshua Marik with a double, leading to Operation Guerrero, which saw Katrina remove the Lyran half of the Federated Commonwealth out of the alliance and renamed the realm the Lyran Alliance. For now, the future of the ex-Archon Prince is unknown. Currently, he is still the commander of the Star League Defense Force and the mighty coalition he used to crush the Smoke Jaguars and stop the rest of the Clan juggernaut.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>INN</service>
		<location>Luthien</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Clan infighting</headline>
		<date>3061-04-23</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Reports are scarce at best, however sources in the Jade Falcon Occupation Zone report that the Falcons came under attack by Clan Steel Viper at the start of the month and the Vipers seem to have once again decided to enter into the Inner Sphere. Early in the Clan Invasion the Steel Vipers shared the Falcons invasion corridor, until inter-clan battling resulted in the Falcons forcibly ejecting the Vipers from their space. While the inter-clan battling is still somewhat of a mystery to the Inner Sphere, we will have to see if the reappearance of the Steel Vipers means they are here to stay this time or not.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>DBC</service>
		<location>Arc-Royal</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>SLDF defends the St. Ives Compact</headline>
		<date>3061-05-02</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The St. Ives Compact takes heart today as Commanding General Victor Steiner-Davion of the Star League Defense Force has ordered units from the SLDF into action in the St. Ives Compact to stop the Capellan Invasion. General Steiner-Davion has dispatched elements from the elite Eridani Light Horse and Clan Nova Cat to assist the Compact in its fight for continued independence. St. Ives also takes comfort in knowing that heir-apparent Kai Allard-Liao and the elite 1st St. Ives Lancers under his command are en route to return to the Compact to bolster the realm's defense.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>SIBC</service>
		<location>St. Ives</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Clan Nova Cat Alliance</headline>
		<date>3061-06-10</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>After Clan Nova Cat's formal induction into the reborn Star League, Coordinator Theodore Kurita has granted our new Nova Cat allies complete autonomy in the Irece Prefecture. The Nova Cats' great respect for the warrior-traditions of the Combine requested the honor of living in and defending the Combine from our enemies. We look forward to many years of friendship with our new allies.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>VotD</service>
		<location>Luthien</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>8th Free Worlds Legionnaires commissioned</headline>
		<date>3061-06-17</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Today the Free Worlds League Military officially commissioned the 8th Free Worlds Legionnaires, a new BattleMech regiment with air, armor and infantry support units. As with the other Legionnaires regiments, the 8th were recruited from all over the League and the new unit will bolster the defenses along the Federated Commonwealth border.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>GP</service>
		<location>Atreus</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Acamar freed from pirates</headline><!-- Source: Chaos March Sourcebook -->
		<date>3061-08-05</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Today the representative of the Goverment of Acamar stood alongside the representative of the Federated Commonwealth company General Motors to annouced the completion of pacfications campaigns against the pirates and their leader Calvin Noru. We will see how the new government fares in future months.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>INN</service>
		<location>Acamar</location>
	</newsItem>
<!-- Civil War Era (3062 - 3067) -->
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Technical Readout comes available</headline><!-- Source: Technical Readout: 3026 (Revised) -->
		<date>3067-08</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>THe Succession Wars are one of the longest and most destructive in recorded history and Wolf's Dragoons in cooperation with ComStar Publishing have released an updated technical readout from 3026. This new publication addresses some errors from the first printing and has brought new light to some of the more interesting accounts of battles and acts of bravery by pilots and crews.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>MercNet</service>
		<location>Outreach</location>
	</newsItem>
<!-- Jihad Era (3068 - 3080) -->
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Mercenary treachery</headline>
		<date>3068-01-02</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>It seems that for every mercenary command of sterling character (such as Wolf’s Dragoons, the Kell Hounds or the Twelfth Vegan Rangers), there is one for whom money is the only thing that matters. The Word of Blake highlighted this with deadly clarity when they bought Waco’s Rangers, Smithson’s Chinese Bandits, the Tiger Sharks and the 51st Dark Panzer Jaegers and unleashed them on Harlech. Now to this roll of dishonor must be added the Broadsword Legion. Hired by Wolf’s Dragoons in their moment of need, the Legion turned on their employers as the Dragoons battled to defend their homes from the onslaught of the Blakists’ Sixth and Tenth Divisions.<p>At the height of this second battle of Outreach, just as it appeared the defenders were gaining the upper hand, the Broadsword Legion launched a furious assault on the rear of the Dragoons’ Wolf Spiders Battalion. Pinned between the Legion and the Blakist Diplomacy of Force III-Alpha, the Wolf Spiders (proud holders of the Black Widow Battalion legacy) were almost annihilated before they could rally. That costly act of treachery further weakened the Dragoons. In an apparent effort to finish off the famed mercenaries once and for all, the Blakists reportedly launched devastating strategic attacks against the planet from orbit.<p>Across the Inner Sphere, the same question is being asked: Who will next turn their coat? Which mercenary command will turn on its employers and do the evil bidding of the Word of Blake? This fear has already led to tragedy on Epsilon Indi, where the Com Guards Second Division launched an unprovoked attack on the Tooth of Ymir. Reportedly, relations between the Com Guards and the mercenaries had been strained ever since the mercenary unit arrived on-world.<p>Faced with overwhelming odds, Colonel Shadwell wisely ordered the battered Tooth to surrender. Following an exhaustive investigation, Precentor Regis Grandi has reluctantly been forced to concede that no tangible proof exists linking the Tooth with the Word of Blake. The Tooth of Ymir, now under the minimum strength stipulated by their contract, is reportedly headed for Arc-Royal to rebuild. In the meantime, many mercenary commanders are left nervously wondering how long it will be before their equally nervous employers turn on them.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>INN</service>
		<location>Outreach</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Groundbreaking history of the Clan Invasion published</headline><!-- Source: Era Report: 3052 -->
		<date>3075</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>A new book from Avalon Press is breaking records and is being hailed as one of the most complete recollections of the Clan Invasion. <em>Dark Times: The Clan Invasion</em>, has already been listed as one of the fastest selling non-fiction titles to come on the market in the last 200 years.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>FIB</service>
		<location>New Avalon</location>
	</newsItem>
<!-- Dark Age Era (3081+) -->
	<!-- Republic (3081 - 3130) -->
	<!-- Dark Age (3131+) -->
<!-- Non-Canon or Apocryphal Events Section -->
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Hanson's Roughriders spoil pirate drop</headline><!-- Source: Mechwarrior 2: Mercenaries --><!-- Apocryphal -->
		<date>3044-08</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Filed 01 July 3044</p><p>Mercenaries from Hanson's Roughriders on a training mission were surpized when a pirate force attampted to raid Venaria. The recruits and veteran MechWarriors were able to destroy a majority of the pirate BattleMechs before the others surrendered. Debriefings from the field indicated that none of the trainees were injured and that there was no actual risk to the citizens of Venaria as the pirate force was poorly equipped and dropped almost right onto the training area.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>MercNet</service>
		<location>Vanaria</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Galedon V in flames</headline><!-- Source: Mechwarrior 2: Mercenaries --><!-- Apocryphal -->
		<date>3044-09</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Filed 19 August 3044</p><p>The planets in the Galedon system are reporting uprisings against the Draconis garrison forces amid reports of war crimes. Reports are spotty and local media outlets have been supressed by DCMS troops. Both sides are reportedly looking for mercenary units. Several vocal community leaders have been missing recently from the public eye and rumor has it that they have been arrested by Draconis Combine secret police for "reeducation".</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Galedon V</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Peace on Galedon V</headline><!-- Source: Mechwarrior 2: Mercenaries --><!-- Apocryphal -->
		<date>3045-01</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>>Filed 10 December 3044</p><p>Mercenary units and DCMS forces have successfully quelled the destructive uprisings on Galedon V. While there are some humanitarian groups decrying the tactics used by the DCMS forces, there is little media coming from the local news agencies reporting any violations. At least one supplier of military hardware was targeted by the rebels, the Novastar Armaments offices were destroyed early in the fighting and reports indicate that the offices were heavily occupied at the time of the attack. Governor Mosami Horkiro has announced that memorial services for all of those killed will be held next week and that today will be declared a planetary day of remembrance.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Galedon V</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Prosperina Rebels seek revenge for Draconis war crimes</headline><!-- Source: Mechwarrior 2: Mercenaries --><!-- Apocryphal -->
		<date>3045-06-01</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Following the unsuccessful uprisings on Galedon last year the citizens of Prosperina have demanded that Draconis forces turn over anyone responsible for the massacre of civilians that occured last year during the Freedom Marches. So far there has been no word on the capabilities of the rebel groups or if they intend to stage violent military actions against the Draconis Combine leaders.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Prosperina</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Rebel forces bloody DCMS</headline><!-- Source: Mechwarriors 2: Mercenaries --><!-- Apocryphal -->
		<date>3045-10</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>Rebels forces and their hired mercenary units have forced the Draconis Combine leadership to abandon the capital of Prosperina. While the rebels were successful this does not mean that they have abandoned the planet all together. Several military and police leaders that had been identified as participating in the Freedom March incident have been killed in the last few months in combat or during attacks on their places of work or residence. The DCMS has reported that all members of the rebellion and their supporting mercenaries have been branded terrorists and that they will recieve no quarter on their return to the capital. Sources inside the rebel camp have reached out during the fighting to indicate that the DCMS forces attampted to damage several buildings in the city including the Hoto Memorial Hospital and the main water treatment facility. They indicated that the DCMS forces have also been responsible for targeting civilian vehicles and buildings under the guise of engaging rebel forces. There is still no official MRB announcment on the names or statuses of the mercenaries that are employed on Prosperina.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Prosperina</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Out of the freezer and into the fire</headline><!--- Source: Mechwarrior 2: Mercenaries --><!-- Apocryphal -->
		<date>3047-01</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>An unprecedented attempt to help the citizens of Liezen is currently underway in the space above the planet. The Inner Sphere's largest iceburg has been towed into place near the planet and is awaiting breakup into managable pieces. The burg, dubbed the "Ice Ship", was collected near the outer band of the solar system and is actually close to five-billion tons of icy material compounded from the atmosphere of Fiytov, the furthest planet in the system. Several mecenary units have been reportedly identified on the surface of the ship to discourage raids or sabotage of this essential mission.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Liezen</location>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<headline>Ice Ship attacked! Mercenaries prevent catastrophic outcome</headline><!-- Source: Mechwarrior 2: Mercenaries --><!-- Apocryphal -->
		<date>3047-05</date>
		<desc><![CDATA[<p>The mercenary units aboard the Liezen Ice Ship prevented an event that would have cost the lives of tens of thousands of people on the surface of Liezen. An unknown force attacked the Ice Ship with several aerospace fighters and BattleMechs attempting to disable the engines and cause the ship to crash into the surface of the planet. While the mercenaries held off the attackers their JumpShip and DropShips fled the system leaving no indication as to the alliegence of the force. The governor of Liezen announced that the mercenaries will recieve a large bonus from the thankful populace as well as several days of complementary arrangements on the surface.</p>]]></desc>
		<service>CNB</service>
		<location>Liezen</location>
	</newsItem>
</news>